The hysteria about the serial killer has triggered public fear.

She's usually pretty good with dealing with emotion, but when her mother died, she was hysterical.

The fans were at fever pitch when the team turned the game around.

I'm gonna pictch my idea to my boss/in the meeting.

Pitch perfect.

I suspected that he stole my wallet.

The main suspect of this murder case is the victim's husband.

He looks suspicious.

You look kind of suspicious with that mustache.

The innocent little girl.

Stop being so naive, he's definitely cheating on you.