1. 
(1) surround = thing around another thing
                     = very common (in this video)

(2) surroundings (n.) = your current environment
    -> Take a look at your surroundings.

2. 
(1) emotionless = no motions = very robotic
     -> The piece of art work is very emotionless.

(2) emotion (n.) 感覺、感情

(3) emotional (a.) 
    -> sb. is very emotional.
        (It could be a negative adjective which describes someone who is overly sensitive or not logical. It could also be used to describe someone who is self-aware.)

3. 
(1) automated (a.) 
    -> All the manufacturing processes in the company have become fully automated.
    -> I emailed a company, but I just got an automated response.  

(2) automatic (a.) = something does something on its own
    -> Back in my day, car doesn't have an automatic door. 
    (When I was young, we don't have doors on the car that can open on their own.)
    * Back in my day, (a classic, old person to say)
       ~ In my generation,
       ~ When I was your age, 

(3) automation (n.) = the concept of making things automatic/automated
    -> While we are losing many jobs to offshoring, we are losing even more  automation.
    * offshoring = job moves to outside of the country

(4) autonomy (n.) = an independent right to self-govern  
    -> With this new government,  all of the provinces will have greater autonomy.
    (Now that we have this new government, each of the provinces will have more power to make their own decisions.)
    * province = state = 州

automobile = a machine that can move (ex. car)
autobiography = a biography about your own life
biography = a story about someone's life 
--------
We're now surrounded by so many voices that are emotionless. You know, by these automated voices that sound very fake. Where it's like, "I'd love to help you, I'm a computer that's here to help you with whatever you want all the time."