Toll:代價，過路費。

Fee = Charge. Ex: The food is already expensive, and then they add an extra 10% service charge.

Heroism:英雄主義
Communism:共產主義

As a perfectionist, Jonny couldn’t bear making any mistakes during his first speech.

Sane(adj.)頭腦清楚的

The scientist went insane and proclaimed that he is developing some kind of dangerous weapon that can destroy the world.

Amy is a very ambitious entrepreneur and she is eager to increase market share of company’s product.