Not least 可翻為「尤其是、特別是、其中重要的是」
比如說: Melody couldn't sync her phone-recording with the internet's, not least because the latest version of Voicetube app may have an uncanny problem with IOS system....

My doctor told me that my headache was induced by working under pressure for a long time.

Even though tomorrow is my final report's deadline, I was seduced by the good weather(被好天氣誘惑) and decided to go to the beach with my friends.

Vengeance(N)

Take revenge on someone. 
Ex: My boss told me that we are taking revenge on that department by revealing their mistakes during the meeting.

Avenge A on B(替A向B報仇) 
Ex: The superhero vowed to avenge his father(為父親復仇).

The representative spoke on behalf of the students to express the dissatisfaction towards the new policy.

Behavioral=Behavioural(英式)
Ex: Behavioral science involves the process of analyzing the behavior of human beings and animals through the study of the past. 
