一個很常用的phrase: An uncanny resemblance.形容難以解釋的相似處。

Our ultimate goal is to convince the company to support the new project.

She hadn't told me the approximate(adj.) time of arrival, so I don't know when I should pick her up.

The length of the pool is approximated(v in past term) as 25 meters. 

Of course the two girls resemble each other, they are twins.

The song you just played is similar to the one I heard in the restaurant yesterday.

I can't wait to see the new movie, the cast(卡司) is really strong.

The actor played the role in the movie as Harry Potter.

Leading role and supporting role.主角及配角

Best actor/actress in leading role

Best actor/actress in supporting role.