A spooky(陰森怪異的) video.／

Horror can be a genre of movie. It's also like an emotion, an extreme fear.／

You are horrified if you get extremely horror.／

It's horrific[hɔrˋrɪfɪk]/horrifying = It's very scary and causes us extremely shocked and scared at the same time.／

All of the crime scenes were horrific to look at.／

Nowadays, "horrible" just means something is very bad.

All of this bowl of noodle is horrible/terrible/awful.／

"Hideous" just means super super super ugly.／

It's almost one step above hideous, it's the word "repulsive". Repulsive(使人反感的) not only means it looks ugly, but it also causes a negative reaction that sort of affects you.／

In some definitions, you have to be published in order to be considered an author(作家，作者). For example, Stephen King is an example of author.／

For the word Writer(作者), it is more general. You're not necessarily published. And pretty often I should mention that these words are used to talk to author and writer, are used interchangeably. In most cases, these(author and writer) are gonna be the same thing.／

If you are a novelist you write....all together on three, one, two, novel. XDDDD／