1. 
    * exercise  [ˋɛksɚ͵saɪz]  (n.)  運動，鍛鍊；練習；習題
      *	sport：通常跟球類及輸贏有關。
      *	sport是exercise，但exercise不一定是sport。
    * exercise  [ˋɛksɚ͵saɪz]  (v.)  練習；運動
      *	= moving your body
      - I exercise every morning.
        + 我每天早上運動。
2. 
    * chipper  [ˋtʃɪpɚ]  (adj.)  爽朗的；活潑的；精力充沛的；身體好的
      - He's quite chipper today.
        + 他今天心情及精神很好。
3. 
    * scale  [skel]  (n.)  刻度；尺度；刻度尺；比率；縮尺
4. 
    * feel  [fil]  (v.)  有感覺；覺得[L]；摸索；摸索著尋找
      - I feel sick. (~ I am sick.)
        + 我覺得我生病了。
    * feel like  [fil laɪk]  (v.)  摸上去如同；感覺好似
      - I feel like eating chocolate.
        + 我感覺好像在吃巧克力。(實際上沒在吃)
--------------------------------------
I think exercising in the morning helped me stay a little more chipper. I felt more confident today. I would say, on a scale from zero to 10, I feel about a seven.

我覺得在早晨慢跑使我比較神清氣爽，我今天比較有信心。我會說，從零到十的等級我感覺有七。