1. _
	* face-to-face  (phr.)(adv.)(adj.)  面對面地；面對著的
		- I think it would be best to talk face-to-face about this.
		- I think it would be best to have a face-to-face conversation about this.
			+ 我認為最好就此進行面對面的交談。
	* head-to-head  (phr.)(adv.)(adj.)  正面對抗地；正面對抗的
		- In a direct competition or contest against someone or something else.
		- The boxers go head-to-head tomorrow.
			+ 拳擊手明天會面對面對抗。

2. _
	* express  [ɪkˋsprɛs]  (v.)  表達
		- I find it's hard to express myself using English.
			+ 我覺得很難用英語來表達自己。
	* expression  [ɪkˋsprɛʃən]  (n.)  表達；表情
		- The way that someone's face looks and this shows their emotions and their feelings.
		- I could tell by Howard's expression that he was disappointed.
			+ 霍華德的表情表示他很失望。

3. _
	* go at  (phr.)  攻擊; 撲向
		- This phrase is not very formal. It's usually used in spoken English or in less formal settings.(口語)
		- When the teacher went outside, she saw the students going at each other.
			- 當老師出門時，她看到學生們互相攻擊。
	* go off on sb.  (phr.)  突然變得很憤怒
		- in spoken English
		- Suddenly rage.
		- When Billy came home late, his mom went off on him. => Billy's mom went off on him. It means that she suddenly started getting angry at him.
			+ 當Billy晚回家的時候，他的媽媽突然對他很生氣。
	* go for sb.  (phr.)  襲擊（某人）；攻擊（某人)
		- When the robber broke into the house, the dog went for him.
			+ 當強盜闖進房子時，狗去攻擊他。

