1. _
	* turn out  (phr.)  結果是；證明是
		- The event turned out to be a success.
			+ 這次活動取得了成功。
	* work out  (phr.)  按某種方式發展；結果
		~ have a good result.
		- Everything will work out. Don't worry.
			+ 一切都會成功，不用擔心。
	* pan out  (phr.)  發展、結果；成功
		~ To end up or conclude especially successfully.
		- We'll just have to wait and see how everything pans out.
			+ 我們只需要等待，看看一切如何成功。
		-  The deal didn't pan out <=> The deal didn't work out <=> The deal was not successful.
			+ 這件交易不成功

2. _
	* pipes  [paɪps]  (n.)  嗓子
		~ Have a big set of pipes = have a loud voice. Or to say someone has a great singing voice.
		- Tina has a fantastic set of pipes. and that would mean that she has a fantastic voice.
			+ 蒂娜的嗓子很棒，這意味著她的聲音很棒。
	* belt out  (phr.)  放聲高唱；大聲播放
		~ to sing a song loudly and energetically. 
		- He belted out his favorite song at karaoke.
			+ 他在KTV放聲高唱他最喜歡的歌曲

3. _
	* attitude  [ˋætətjud]  (n.)  態度
		- Sally always has a positive attitude.
		~ Attitude can also mean a way of thinking or behaving people think of unfriendly or rude or something bad.
		- Don't give me attitude <=> Don't act in this way, Don't be unfriendly or rude.
			+ 不要用那種態度(通常是家長對小孩說的話)
	* talk back  (phr.)  頂嘴
		~ to answer someone in authority (parents or teachers) in a rude way
		- Cindy got sent to her room for talking back to her dad.
			+ Cindy在她的房間與她爸爸頂嘴。
.................................

Turns out, tiny dogs, like the Yorkshire Terrier, tend to have a big set of pipes with an even bigger attitude.
原來小型犬，像是約克夏，通常吠得大聲，態度上更是傲慢。
