Mouths are dirty, dark, moist places, full of breeding bacteria. In fact, one mouth can contain more bacteria than there are people on Earth!
嘴巴是一個骯髒、黑暗、潮濕的地方，充滿了繁殖的細菌；事實是，一張嘴巴可以容納的細菌比地球上的人類還多！

1. _
    * moist  [mɔɪst]  (adj.)  潮濕的
        - Keep the soil moist so that the seeds can grow.
            + 保持土壤濕潤，使種子生長。
        - My favorite dessert is moist chocolate cake.
            + 我最喜歡的甜點是鬆軟潮濕的巧克力蛋糕。
    * humid  [ˋhjumɪd]  (adj.)  濕熱的
        - Many people can't stand the humid weather in Taiwan.
            - 很多人受不了台灣潮濕的天氣。
    * damp  [dæmp]  (adj.)  濕冷的
        - The house is cold and damp.
            + 房子又冷又濕。

2. _
    * breed  [brid]  (v.)  繁殖、孕育
        - His main income comes from breeding fish.
            + 他的主要收入來自繁殖魚類。
    * cultivate  [ˋkʌltə͵vet]  (v.)  耕作、養殖
        - 用於農耕
        - Most of the land here is suitable for cultivating rice.
            + 這裡的大部分土地都適合種植水稻。

3. _
    * bacteria  [bækˋtɪrɪə]  (n.)  細菌
        - bacteria => bacterium（單數）
        - Wear a mask to prevent from being infected by bacteria.
            + 戴口罩以防止被細菌感染。
    * virus  [ˋvaɪrəs]  (n.)  病毒
        - The flu virus infected almost the whole class.
            + 流感病毒幾乎感染了整個班級。
    * infect  [ɪnˋfɛkt]  (v.)  傳染、感染