Hi guys, welcome to today's pronunciation challenge, and my name is Kristi. So with the heavy heart, this would be my last day on the Pronunciation Challenge.
And like I said you will be hearing me on the weekends perhaps. But hmm this is going to be my very last day here. And hmm today we have a video from The School of Life
and it's called You Are Not What You Earn. So perhaps we're living(此處不確定@@) in the society where people are sometimes defined by their salary, or by what they do, or by how much they earn for a living. But hmm this video tells us otherwise, because that is really not the important thing in life. So let's take a look.

Wages are simply the result of the intensity with which certain people want a job done relative to the number of people who happen to be able to do it.

---------------------------------------------------
1-1. wage  [wedʒ]  (n.)  薪水、報酬 (工資)
# salary 指薪水本身
# minimum wage 最低工資
# compensation 補償、酬勞、年薪/薪水總稱(美國口語用法)  

1-2. wedge  [wɛdʒ]  (n.)  楔形
e.g. potato wedges  楔形薯條 

--------------
2-1. intensity  [ɪnˋtɛnsətɪ]  (n.)  強度
e.g. I really like today's sporting course, but the intensity was rather high for me.

2-2. intense  [ɪnˋtɛns]  (adj.)  強烈的,緊繃的
e.g. An intense odor
e.g. The situation has gotten intense.

2-3. intensify  [ɪnˋtɛnsə͵faɪ]  (v.)  使...變激烈
e.g. He backed out of the argument when it intensified.

---------
3-1. result  [rɪˋzʌlt]  (n.) 結果  (v.)
e.g. exam result / result of the examination (n.)
e.g. His lack of practice resulted in a mistake in the competition. (v.)

3-2. consequence  [ˋkɑnsə͵kwɛns]  (n.)  結果(含有一點"後果"的概念/前因後果)
e.g. You can make whatever decision you want, but remember to be responsible for whatever the consequence it has.
----------
4-1. certain  [ˋsɝtən]  (adj.)  確鑿的、無疑的
#it is for certain 無庸置疑的
e.g. It is for certain that it will not rain tomorrow.  

4-2. certainly  [ˋsɝtənlɪ]  (adv.)  確實
e.g. Q: Would you like to eat out tonight? A: Certainly.(較正式,現通常用OK/Sure代之)

------------------
Alright so that's it for today's pronunciation challenge. And this will be my last entry on Voicetube. Hmm I have seen all your posts on Tuesday and I have received all of them. And it's definitely it's really heartwarming for me. 
And hmm 我每一個字字句句我真的都有看(真的嗎?)，然後當然最要感謝的就是你們了(OH Yeah~那應該有包含我在內~^^)，
因為其實沒有你們撐起這個口說挑戰我也不會繼續主持下去(可是....)，那今天能有這麼多人在上面交流啊，在上面一起學英文，在上面就是跟大家一起進步發音，我覺得真得是最溫暖的一件事情了!Voicetube有你們這群使用者呢，真的會是我們的福氣，那大家要記得呢，繼續練英文!不管是用什麼管道，只要每天有在持續做這件事情呢,你們就真的一定會進步!
Alright that's pretty much for today, remember to leave your recordings below, and Sam will challenge you guys tomorrow. Bye~ 
(這是我聽了數百遍以來，感觸最深的Bye了...)
