We're often told to drink around 8 glasses of water a day to keep healthy, but the honest truth is that this specific number is somewhat arbitrary, and no scientific research exists to support it.


-------------------------------------------
1 . specific  特殊的
specific  [spɪˋsɪfɪk]  (adj.)  特殊的
＊He was being very specific about no visits to the haunted house, so I guess we should take that out of our itinerary(旅程).

specify  [ˋspɛsə͵faɪ]  (v.)  具體指定
＊This order specifies no ice on all drinks.
＊Please specify about your experiences.

2 . arbitrary  武斷的
arbitrary  [ˋɑrbə͵trɛrɪ]  (adj.)  武斷的
＊Most arbitrary labels are the result of socialization. 

3 . research  研究
research  [rɪˋsɝtʃ]  (n.)  研究 (v.)
＊He researched about the possibilities of aliens in this universe.
＊With a little bit of research, she finally realized that abortion is an inhuman thing to do.

researcher  [riˋsɝtʃɚ]  (n.)  研究員

4 . support  支撐、支援
support  [səˋport]  (v.)  支撐、支援 （實體or精神層面）
＊This pole is the support for the entire ceiling.
＊I really support you whatever you do.
＊Apple watch only supports ios system.

supportive  [səˋpɔrtɪv]  (adj.)  支持的 （精神層面）
＊My parents have always been so supportive of whatever decisions I make.

5 . somewhat 有點，稍微
somewhat  [ˋsʌm͵hwɑt]  (adv.) 有點，稍微
＊We were somewhat tired after our long walk. 走了很長的路之後，我們有些累了。
