Look, your brain always wants to relax. It tries to avoid anything that will force him to work by promising you that you will get a better opportunity in the future.
是這樣的，你的大腦在絕大多數的時候都想要放鬆。它會讓你以下次會更好的想法去避開任何會逼它運作的事物。
.............................

1. _
	* relax  [rɪˋlæks]  (v.)  放鬆；緩和
		- This summer, I decided to travel abroad alone to relax and take a break from the stresses of raising a child.
			+ 今年夏天，我決定獨自出國旅遊以放鬆身心，從養育孩子的壓力中休息一下。
	* relative  [ˋrɛlətɪv]  (adj.)  相對的；相關的
		- Relative to the hard work she put in, her grades were incredibly poor.
			+ 相對於她的成績，她的成績非常差。
	* relative  [ˋrɛlətɪv]  (n.)  親屬；親戚
		- I only see those distant relatives during New Year, so I barely know them.
			+ 我只在新年期間看到那些遠房親戚，所以我幾乎不認識他們。

2. _
	* avoid  [əˋvɔɪd]  (v.)  避開；避免
		- Ever since the last time I embarrassed myself in front of him. I have been avoiding him.
			+ 自從上次以來，我在自己面前尷尬。 我一直在躲避他。
	* avid  [ˋævɪd]  (adj.)  渴望的；貪心的；熱心的
		- She became an avid football fan ever since the last time she watched the World Cup.
			+ 自從她上次看世界杯以來，她成為了一名狂熱的足球迷

3. _
	* force  [fors]  (v.)  強迫；迫使
		- Please don't force your child to do things they don't want to do.
			+ 請不要強迫孩子做他們不想做的事情。
	* enforce  [ɪnˋfors]  (v.)  實施、執行；強制
		- It's more difficult to enforce the law than to make it.
			+ 執行法律比制定法律更加困難。

4. _
	* promise  [ˋprɑmɪs]  (v.)  允諾；答應
		- He promised to love her and to take care of her no matter what.
			+ 無論怎樣，他都答應愛她並照顧她。
	* promising   [ˋprɑmɪsɪŋ]  (adj.)  有希望的；有前途的
		- Every parent hopes their kids can have a promising future.
			+ 每個家長都希望他們的孩子有一個充滿希望的未來。

5. _
	* opportunity  [͵ɑpɚˋtjunətɪ]  (n.)  機會；良機
		- You always need to prepare yourself in order to seize an opportunity when it comes.
			+ 你總是需要做好準備，以便在機會到來時抓住機會。
	* chance  [tʃæns]  (n.)  機遇；機會；時機
		- Please give me a second chance. I promise I'll do it right this time.
			+ 請再給我一次機會，我保證這次我會做對的選擇。
	* opportunity 代表絕對正面的機會，正向的希望。 / chance 是有風險的機會，不一定會成功。
		- take a chance on sth.