The ability to recognize sounds and identify their location is possible thanks to the auditory system. That’s comprised of two main parts: the ear and the brain.
成功識別並且定位聲音來源都多虧於聽覺，系統系統有兩大組成：耳朵和大腦。
..............................

1. _
 * ability [əˋbɪlətɪ] (n.) 能力；能耐 [+to-v]；才能
 - 有能力做某件事
 - ability + to V (do something)
 - She never doubts her ability to accomplish these tasks.
 + 她從不懷疑她完成這些任務的能力。
 * capability [kepəˋbɪlətɪ] (n.) 能力、才能；性能、功能；耐受力
 - 形容可以或不可以做某件事
 - capability for / of + N, to + V(do something)
 - The exam is beyond the capabilities of most high school students.
 + 考試超出了大多數高中生的能力。
 * ability, capability 大多數時候可以互相取代。
 - I have the ability to write doesn't mean I have the capability to write the 15-page paper by tomorrow.
 + 我有能力寫作並不意味著我有能力在明天之前寫出15頁的論文。
 - I might say that will I have the ability to write. I don't have the capability to write a novel.
 + 我可能會說我有能力寫作。我沒有寫小說的能力。

2. _
 * recognize [ˋrɛkəg͵naɪz] (v.) 認出；認識；正式承認；認可
 - I haven't seen you for so long. I almost didn't recognize you.
 + 我好久沒有見到你了，差點認不出你。
 * recognition [rɛkəgˋnɪʃən] (n.) 認出，識別；認可
 - He's yearning for the recognition of his parents.
 + 他渴望得到父母的認可。

3. _
 * identify [aɪˋdɛntə͵faɪ] (v.) 確認；識別；鑑定
 - After a certain age, it becomes very difficult to identify the different sounds that do not exist in our native language.
 + 在一定年齡之後，我們難識別出我們母語中，不存在的音。
 * identity [aɪˋdɛntətɪ] (n.) 身分；本身；本體
 - He doesn't have a strong national identity.
 + 他沒有強烈的民族認同感。
 + national identity. => 民族(國家)認同

4. _
 * auditory [ˋɔdə͵torɪ] (adj.) 耳朵的；聽覺的；聽到的
 - The noise in our daily life can cause irreversible damage to auditory cells.
 + 我們日常生活中的噪音會對聽覺細胞造成不可逆轉的損害。
 * audit [ˋɔdɪt] (n.) 審計；查帳；決算; 旁聽生(美)
 - The company is required to have an audit at the end of each financial year.
 + 公司必須在每個財政年度結束時進行審計。

5. _
 * comprise [kəmˋpraɪz] (v.) 包含，包括；由……組成
 + The US is comprised of 50 states.
 + 美國包括50個州。
 * compose [kəmˋpoz] (v.) 組成、構成
 - be composed of ... 由 .. 構成
 - His audience is composed of mostly middle-aged people, aged 40 to 60.
 + 他的觀眾主要是40至60歲的中年人。