Making your bed will also reinforce the fact that the little things in life matter. If you can't do the little things right, you'll never be able to do the big things right. And if you by chance you have a miserable day, you will come home to a bed that is made.
摺好棉被也會強化一件事，就是生命中的每件小事都很重要。如果你無法把小事做好，你也難以做大事。如果今天好巧不巧，你有個悲慘的一天，至少你回家時，有整理好的床在等妳。
...............

1. _
	* reinforce  [͵riɪnˋfɔrs]  (v.)  強化，加深
		- His constant excuses merely reinforce my dislike for him.
			+ 他不斷的藉口使我更加不喜歡他。
		- Q-learning is a kind of Reinforcement learning.
	* reincarnation  [͵riɪnkɑrˋneʃən]  (n.)  轉世化身
		- He believes he's the reincarnation of William Shakespeare. I believe he needs to see the doctor.
			+ 他相信他是威廉·莎士比亞的轉世化身，我相信他需要去看醫生。

2. _
	* matter  [ˋmætɚ]  (n.)  事情；問題；麻煩事
		- What's the matter with you? I told you not to do this.
			+ 你怎麼了我已經告訴你不要這樣做了？
			+ 生活例句
	* matter-of-fact  [ˋmætərəvˋfækt]  (adj.)  講求實際的；就事論事的
		- 當別人覺得你應該會流露出感情，但實際上就事論事。
		- His tone is purely matter-of-fact when he speaks of the incident.
			+ 當他談到這件事時，他純粹是在談論事實。

3. _
	* able  [ˋeb!]  (adj.)  能；可以；有能力的
		- She's able to help take care of her little brother when she was only 5 years old.
			+ 當她只有5歲時，她能夠幫助照顧她的弟弟。
			+ be able to ... 能夠做到
	* able  [ˋeb!]  (adj.)  有能力的
		- Mike's mentor is an able lawyer.
			+ Mike的導師是一位幹練的律師。

4. _
	* by chance  (ph.)  意外地；偶然
		- He ran into his boss by chance yesterday and had coffee together.
			+ 他昨天偶然遇到了他的老闆，一起喝咖啡。
			+ ran into 遇到了
	* by any chance  (ph.)  或許; 可能；萬一
		- Could you lend me some money by any chance?
			+ 你有機會藉給我一些錢嗎？
	* chance your arm  (ph.)  冒險做某件事= take a risk.
		- Don't chance your arm by giving up your regular job to be a freelance writer.
			+ 不要放棄正常工作來成為自由撰稿人。
			+ Don't chance your arm (doing something)

5. _
	* miserable  [ˋmɪzərəb!]  (adj.)  痛苦的；不幸的
		- He enjoys making my life miserable. I hate him so much.
			+ 他喜歡讓我的生活變得悲慘，我非常討厭他。
			+ 好用的句子。
	* misery  [ˋmɪzərɪ]  (n.)  痛苦；不幸
		- The movie has let us to witness the most appalling scenes of human misery.
			+ 這部電影讓我們見證了最慘不忍睹的人間苦難。