Color is a term that we use to describe a collection of attributes, hue and saturation and value, that describes how we see things.
就是...你知道 no pun intended (其實我沒有別的意思) 這句片語嗎？這應該是要說明你不小心說了一些好笑的事。喔，你知道的，像是，「這個飛行員的職涯就要起飛了。」
.................

1. _
	* pun  [pʌn]  (n.)  雙關語；俏皮話
		- pun is a joke that takes advantage of different possible meanings of a word.
		- Two meanings.
		- reland has the fast growing population. Every day it’s doubling. 不是Dublin喔XD. No pun intended. It’s really funny to me. 
2. _
	* intend  [ɪnˋtɛnd]  (v.)  想要；打算
		- To plan.
3. _
	* supposed  [səˋpozd]  (adj.)  假定的；想像上的；被信以為真的
		- That's assumed the believed to be the case but not necessarily.
4. _
	* mean  [min]  (v.)  意思
		- Definition.
5. _
	* by accident  [baɪ ˋæksədənt]  (ph.)  偶然, 意外地
		- It's a phrase and it's just means something that you do not plan to do.
6. _
	* career  [kəˋrɪr]  (n.)  職業
		- This job is for your whole life so any job and job that pays the bills and gives you money may not be your career and maybe just temporary. A career such as something that you want to do until you retired.
7. _
	* take off  [tek ɔf]  (ph.)  (飛機)起飛; 突然大受歡迎
		- Take off has numerous meanings. If it's a plane and means to fly. If it's a career, in this case, it means to get more money to get a promotion to rise quickly.

...........................

When you say something that has double meaning, you realized that not only have you said <Not only...but （also）的倒裝文法> what you intended to say, but it has another meaning. You can use the phrase: No pun intended.

I’m a big fan of whiteboards. I find them quite remarkable/re-markable.(the key to the pun：非凡的/可重覆標記的）
