Here's the issue with computer updates right, is they give me the opportunity to procrastinate on a silver platter. How are you gonna expect me, me, to make the right decision when you're so easily presenting me with an option to do this task tomorrow.
電腦更新有個重點那就是它有個拖延，你怎麼能夠在期望我做出正確決定的同時，給了我一個「明天再更新」的選項。
...............................

1. 
issue[ˋɪʃjʊ] (n.)問題
->They are discussing the major issue of campus security in the conference room.
->Global warming issue
have issues[hæv ˋɪʃjʊ] (v.)有問題；有分歧
->Kelly dumped her boyfriend because he has some issues with her friends.
issue[ˋɪʃjʊ] (v.)發行；發布
->He is forced to issue a statement about the tragic accident for the company.
2. 
update[ʌpˋdet] (v.)更新
->computer update
->The update the version of the software is better and more efficient than the old one.
up to date(ph.)現代的；最近的
->The first thing Kelly does is to keep herself up to date with the latest gossip.
3.
procrastinate[proˋkræstə͵net] (v.)延遲；耽擱
->I always procrastinate when it comes to homework.
->Do your homework, don’t procrastinate. 
procrastinator[pro͵kræstə͵netɚ] (n.)拖延者，有拖延症
->I never study until the night before finals because I am a procrastinator.
procrastination[pro͵kræstəˋneʃən] (n.)拖延
->There’s no time for procrastination, we need to decide right now.
4. 
on a silver platter(ph.)輕易得手；拱手相讓
->If we sell our share in the company now, we’re handing the ownership to them on a silver platter.
platter[ˋplætɚ] (n.)大淺盤(通常為橢圓形)
->They put five kinds of cheese on the wooden platter.
