1. 
a. secrete  [sɪˋkrit]  (v.)  【生理】分泌(唾液、汗水...)
  * 重音在第二音節

b. secret  [ˋsikrɪt]  (n.)  祕密
  * 重音在第一音節
  -> If you tell my secret to others, don’t show up in my life again.
    如果你把我的秘密說出去，我們就絕交。

c. tear  [tɪr]  (n.)  眼淚
  -> Teardrops On My Guitar
    淚灑吉他(歌名)

d. saliva  [səˋlaɪvə]  (n.)  唾液

2.
a. pore  [por]  (n.)  毛孔

b. pimple  [ˋpɪmp!]  (n.)  粉刺、青春痘
  -> Pimples form when pores become blocked with dirt.
    會長粉刺跟青春痘是因為毛孔倍灰塵和髒東西堵住了。

3.
a. evaporate  [ɪˋvæpə͵ret]  (v.)  蒸發、消失
  -> His anger evaporated as the misunderstanding was explained.
    當誤會解除，他的憤怒就消失了。

b. vanish  [ˋvænɪʃ]  (v.)  消失
  -> When I turned around, that girl had vanished.
    當我轉身時，那個女生就已經消失了。

c. evaporated milk  (n.)  煉乳

4.
a. cool down  (phr.)  使…變涼、【口】冷靜一點
  -> Cool down! Don’t be so agitated. 
    冷靜一點！不要這麼激動。

b. calm down  (phr.)  冷靜一點
-------------------------------------
When this sweat is secreted through your pores and evaporated into the air, your body begins to cool down and your overall body temperature returns to normal.