我們移民過頭了嗎？(Has migration gone too far? | The Economist)
Over the past few decades, the reasons for migration have multiplied. Wars, famines and climate change are pushing people from their homes.
在過去的幾十年以來，移民的理由越來越多元。戰爭、饑荒及氣候變遷把人們趕出自己的家園。

1. migration  遷移
    * migration  [maɪˋgreʃən]  (n.)  遷移
        - Problems in the certain countries make cause migration to increase.
    * migrate  [ˋmaɪ͵gret]  (v.)  遷移
        - Many people from rural areas migrate to urban areas.
        - The birds migrate self in the winter.
    * immigrate  [ˋɪmə͵gret]  (v.)  遷入
        - My family immigrated to Canada when I was young.

2. multiply  增加；相乘
    * multiply  [ˋmʌltəplaɪ]  (v.)  增加；相乘
        - At my new job, my responsibilities have multiplied.
        - Two multiplied by five is ten.
    * multiple  [ˋmʌltəp!]  (adj.)  多樣的
        - This plan has multiple problems.
    * multiplication  [͵mʌltəpləˋkeʃən]  (n.)  增加；乘法
        - We learn multiplication during math class.

3. famine  饑荒
    * famine  [ˋfæmɪn]  (n.)  饑荒
        - In the 1800 there was a famine in Ireland due to problems with potato crops.
    * famished  [ˋfæmɪʃt]  (adj.)  非常飢餓的
        - After a day of hiking, I was famished.

4. climate change  氣候變化
    * climate change  (phr.)  氣候變化
        - Climate change is a major problem in our world today.
    * global warming  (phr.)  全球氣溫上升
        - Global warming may cause glaciers to melt.