Chances are if you play more than 5-10 hours of action games a week, you're able to solve these problems much more quickly. This is because your brain is actually more efficient in the regions associated with attention.
────────────────────────
【影片筆記】
●get ahead (取得進展；獲得成功)
Before we get ahead of ourselves, it's important to note that too much of anything is bad--even broccoli! 
在我們繼續下去之前，重要的是要注意任何東西過量都不好，連花椰菜也是！

■binge (v.) 狂歡作樂 (n.) 狂歡作樂；放縱；（尤指在飲食和花錢方面）無節制的狂熱行為
So if you binge and do nothing but play video games, the risks probably outweigh any benefits.
所以，如果你很放縱又什麼都沒做，只有打電動遊戲，風險可能會大於任何好處。

■dyslexia (n.) 閱讀障礙症
■dyslexic (adj./n.) 有讀寫障礙的(人)
They may even help kids who suffer from Dyslexia read more effectively.
這些遊戲甚至能幫助受閱讀障礙而苦的小孩讀得更有效率。

In a small study, dyslexic children who played regular video games ended up reading faster and more accurately.
在一項小型研究中，有玩固定電動遊戲的閱讀障礙小孩，最後閱讀的速度更快也更精確。

■remote-controlled tools (遙控工具)
Finally, as technology continues to transform medicine, surgeries are being completed with the insertion of cameras and remote-controlled tools.
最後，隨著科技不斷改變醫學，相機的嵌入和遙控工具讓手術變得完整。

■downtime (n.) 停機時間；停工期；不工作時間
↔ uptime (n.) (計算機等的) 正常運行時間
So enjoy your downtime and relax with your games in moderation but get out there and keep your life diverse as well, because that's how you'll win at the game of life!
所以，享受你的閒暇時間，並適度地用你的遊戲來放鬆，但也要出去保持你生活多采多姿，因為這就是你如何在人生遊戲中獲勝的方法！
────────────────────────
