The depressed phase of bipolar disorder manifests in many ways - a low mood, dwindling interest in hobbies, 
changes in appetite, feeling worthless or excessively guilty, sleeping either too much or too little, 
restlessness or slowness, or persistent thoughts of suicide.

而躁鬱症的鬱期會以不同方式出現：情緒低落、漸漸對自己的嗜好不感興趣、食慾改變、感到自己一無是處或過於內疚、睡眠過多或過少、
坐立不安或行動緩慢或是不斷有自殺的想法。(全球大約有三分之一的成年人有非常多的症狀，顯示他們有躁鬱症。)

1 . manifest  顯然的 

manifest  [ˋmænə͵fɛst]  (adj.)  顯然的、(v.) 表明，顯示，表露
Imagination is a force that can actually manifest a reality.

2 . appetite  胃口 

appetite  [ˋæpə͵taɪt]  (n.)  胃口 
I don’t have an appetite right now.

appetizer  [ˋæpə͵taɪzɚ]  (n.)  開胃菜、前菜

3 . dwindle  變小 

dwindle  [ˋdwɪnd!]  (v.)  變小 
She dwindled herself in order to fit into the categories that she likes.

4 . excessively  過度地 

excessively  [ɪkˋsɛsɪvlɪ]  (adv.)  過度地 
He has been excessively working.

excessive  [ɪkˋsɛsɪv]  (adj.)  過度的 
Excessive development has created a natural disaster all around the world.

5 . persistent  堅持不懈的 

persistent  [pɚˋsɪstənt]  (adj.)  堅持不懈的 
She has always been quite persistent in chasing in the things that she loves.

