This works for the time being, but ultimately only seventy-five percent of the brain's energy requirements can come from ketones. 
It still needs glucose, which means your cognitive functioning becomes impaired. 

這種方式能夠持續一段時間，但最終只有百分之七十五的大腦能夠吸收來自酮類的能量。
它仍需要葡萄糖，這樣的缺乏表示你的認知功能會受到損傷。

1 . ultimately  最終地 

ultimately  [ˋʌltəmɪtlɪ]  (adv.)  最終地 
You may think that a great idea to avoid the problem right now, but ultimately you will have to face it.
雖然你現在迴避這個問題看起來像是個不錯的解決辦法，可是最終你遲早還是要來面對它。

ultimate  [ˋʌltəmɪt]  (adj.)  最後的 

2 . requirement  需求 

requirement  [rɪˋkwaɪrmənt]  (n.)  需求 
She seems like a strong candidate, and it’s unfortunate that she still didn't meet the requirement.
她雖然看起來像是個非常好的人選，但是她仍然沒有達到我們所需求的條件。

require  [rɪˋkwaɪr]  (v.)  需要 
This position requires a passion for translation.
這個職位非常需要對翻譯的熱誠。

acquire  [əˋkwaɪr]  (v.)  取得、獲得 
Pursue only what you can and should acquire; never pursue what you can’t and shouldn’t acquire.
你應該要追求自己有能力追求到的然後你應該要追求到的東西；不要去追求你沒辦法得到的。

3 . cognitive  認知的 

cognitive  [ˋkɑgnətɪv]  (adj.)  認知的 
cognitive function 大腦的認知功能

cognition  [kɑgˋnɪʃən]  (n.)  認知 

4 . impair  削弱、減少 

impair  [ɪmˋpɛr]  (v.)  削弱、減少 

impaired [ɪmˋpɛrd] (adj.) 受損的；（能力）減弱的
visually impaired 視覺受損的

pair  [pɛr]  (v.)  配對 (n.) 成雙成對
All blue tooth devices need to be paired beforehand.
那些藍芽的裝置使用之前都必須配對。

repair  [rɪˋpɛr]  (v.)  修理 
After being soaked in water, this car needs repairing.
浸水了之後，這輛車必須被好好地修理一番。