Thank Kristi. Happy Chinese New year, everyone.

Because of a limited range, the battery's space improves limited. 
Thus, we are only to improve the software efficiency.
---------------------------------------- 

1-1. battery [ˋbætərɪ]  (n.)
----------

2-1. capacity [kəˋpæsətɪ]  (n.)
* The capacity of this arena is actually fifty thousand people.

2-2. capable [ˋkepəb!]  (adj.)
* I believe that she is capable of finishing such task alone.

---------- 

3-1. trick [trɪk]  (n.)詭計 (v.)欺騙、愚弄
# trick or treat

* He tricked his parents into believing that the school's having a day off today.

----------

4-1. consumption [kənˋsʌmpʃən]  (n.) 

4-2. consume [kənˋsjum]  (v.)
* When we go hiking, we consume more water faster than we thought.
 
4-3. consumer [kənˈsjuː.mər] (n.) 任何商品或任何服務的消費者

4-4. customer [ˈkʌs.tə.mɚ] (n.)一家實體店的顧客
----------

5-1. stagnant [ˋstægnənt]  (adj.) 停滯的
* During hot summers, the business of hot pot restaurants are often stagnant.

---------------------------------------- 

Just this year, the iPhone 7 Plus came out with about an hour more battery life than the iPhone 6S Plus. 
But the battery capacity is only a tiny bit larger. The trick is that what we call 
"battery life" is actually capacity divided by consumption, and while capacity is stagnant, power consumption is not.