Well, your brain has no way of knowing what types of information will be useful in the future, so 
it has a variety of criteria to determine what to hold on to. First, your brain is really great at 
noticing patterns. Repeated facts, sights, sounds, and experiences must all be examined to determine 
whether they're worth remembering or if they should fade from perception. 

你的腦袋無法判定哪些資訊將來是可貴的，所以它有各式各樣的標準來決定該守住甚麼記憶。首先，記起「圖像」
輕而易舉，諸如重複性的事實、影像、聲音、經歷等等，都是檢驗是否值得被記住或是逐漸淡忘的最佳指標。

1 . information  報告 

information  [͵ɪnfɚˋmeʃən]  (n.)  報告、資料
I will need some more extra information in order to get to know this research more.
要知道這份研究我可能需要更多的資料。

inform  [ɪnˋfɔrm]  (v.)  通知、告知 
Oh, sorry! I don’t know any details. I was merely informed that I should substitute her.
我不知道其他細節可是我只是被告知要來替補她的。

2 . variety  多樣化 

variety  [vəˋraɪətɪ]  (n.)  多樣化 
This flagship store has variety of choices.
這家旗艦店有各式各樣的選擇可以讓你選。

vary  [ˋvɛrɪ]  (v.)  使不同 
Sitting preferences vary from people to people.
選座位的偏好因人而異。

3 . criteria  標準、準則 

criteria  [kraɪˋtɪrɪə]  (n.)  標準、準則 (複數)
The criteria while I apply for this school were actually pretty strict since a lot of people wanna get in.
申請這家學校的標準十分嚴苛因為有非常多人想要搶破頭進去。

4 . pattern  花漾、圖案 

pattern  [ˋpætɚn]  (n.)  花漾、圖案 
The pattern on the wallpaper gives me chills.
這個壁紙上面的圖案讓我不太舒服。

5 . determined  果斷的 

determined  [dɪˋtɝmɪnd]  (adj.)  果斷的 
He is determined that he wants to be a pilot one day.
他非常有決心他有一天要變成一個機師。

determine [dɪˋtɝmɪn] (v.) 決定、是…的決定因素
This final competition determines whether or not we’re getting the top three.
在最後一場比賽就會左右我們是否會擠進前三名。

determination  [dɪ͵tɝməˋneʃən]  (n.)  決心 

6 . perception  感知、感覺 

perception  [pɚˋsɛpʃən]  (n.)  感知、感覺 

perceptive  [pɚˋsɛptɪv]  (adj.)  知覺的、洞察力強的、有遠見的
He is quite perceptive and sees the trend of the market.
他非常有遠見也會看到市場的趨勢。

perceive  [pɚˋsiv]  (v.)  察覺、感知 
Nothing is quite as you perceived. There is always another side of the story.
所有東西並不是總是跟你所感覺到的一模一樣，因為事情一體兩面，總是會有另外一面是你不知道的。