What remains to be seen today is how the nature of our relationship with our possessions will change with 
the rise of digital technologies. Many have forecast the demise of physical books and music, but for now, 
at least, this seems premature. Perhaps there will always be something uniquely satisfying about holding 
an object in our hands and calling it our own. 

至今仍有待觀察的是，隨著數位技術的興起，我們與所有物之間關係的性質會如何改變。許多人預測有形的書籍和音樂將會消失，但至少現在還為時過早。或許，總有一些獨特的東西能夠讓我們握有手中並稱之為屬於自己的。

1 . possession  佔有、擁有 

possession  [pəˋzɛʃən]  (n.)  佔有、擁有 
This iPhone is within my possession.
這支iPhone是我的東西。

possess  [pəˋzɛs]  (v.)  掌握 
He possessed the knowledge of training a dragon.
他掌握了馴龍的技巧跟知識。

possessive  [pəˋzɛsɪv]  (adj.)  佔有的 
Sometimes, a girl was acting possessive is because she is afraid to lose.
有時候一個女生佔有慾很強是因為她害怕失去。

obsession [əbˋsɛʃən] (n.) 著迷
He has an obsession with the newest Mario game.
他對於最新的馬利歐遊戲很著迷。

obsess [əbˋsɛs] (v.) 迷住，使著迷；纏住

obsessive [əbˋsɛsɪv] (adj.) 妄想的；使人著迷的；困擾人的

2 . digital  數字的 

digital  [ˋdɪdʒɪt!]  (adj.)  數字的、數位的
The digital clock on the wall
在牆上的數位時鐘

3 . demise  死亡、終止 

demise  [dɪˋmaɪz]  (v.)  死亡、終止 
The demise of physical books and music 
實體的書本與音樂CD、唱片這些東西的逐漸式微或消失

4 . premature  過早的 

premature  [͵priməˋtjʊr]  (adj.)  過早的 
This seems premature.
言之過早了。

mature  [məˋtjʊr]  (adj.)  成熟的 
His attitude becomes more mature.
他的態度越來越成熟了。

I think the timing is mature right now.
我覺得時機成熟了。

naive  [nɑˋiv]  (adj.)  天真的、幼稚的 
Don’t be so naive! The money you donated won’t be put into good use.
你別這麼天真了! 其實你捐出的錢不會被好好利用的。

5 . unique  獨一無二的 

unique  [juˋnik]  (adj.)  獨一無二的、絕無僅有的

special  特別的

6 . satisfy  使滿意 

satisfy  [ˋsætɪs͵faɪ]  (v.)  使滿意 
As you grow older, I think it is harder to satisfy ourselves.
我認為我們人越長越大，好像要使自己滿意都越來越困難了。

satisfaction  [͵sætɪsˋfækʃən]  (n.)  滿足