Of course, these are, by ordinary adult standards, tiny slights. But we don't love by adult standards. 
These small arrows are enough to wound the self that loves to its tender, emotional core. 

這些以大人的標準來說都只是微不足道的小事。但是我們並非以大人的標準來愛人。這些小事都足以傷到我們脆弱、情緒化內心。

1 . ordinary  平凡的 

ordinary  [ˋɔrdn͵ɛrɪ]  (adj.)  平凡的 
Before Harry Potter found out that he got accepted into Hogwarts, he thought he’s just an ordinary little boy.
在哈利波特被霍格華茲錄取之前，他以為他自己僅只是一個平凡的小男孩。

extraordinary  [ɪkˋstrɔrdn͵ɛrɪ]  (adj.)  非比尋常的、非常突出的
I’ve been on a helicopter once when I was in New Zealand and I have to say that the view is definitely extraordinary.
在紐西蘭的時候坐過一次直升機，在上面看到的風景真的非比尋常、十分漂亮。

2 . adult  成年的 

adult  [əˋdʌlt]  (adj.)  成年的 
I am an adult now. I can make my own decisions.
我現在已經成年是個大人了，我可以為自己的人生做決定。

adolescence  [æd!ˋɛsns]  (n.)  青春 
A lot of teenagers are struggling to find their place on the society in adolescence.
很多青少年在青春期的時候都沒辦法在這個社會上找到自己的定位，比如說他們想要甚麼?或者是他們應該要付出甚麼?

3 . standard  標準 

standard  [ˋstændɚd]  (n.)  標準 
The standard procedure for this emergency is that we should call the police first.
碰到這種緊急事件的標準程序是我們要先叫警察。

How could you be so strict on others but not on yourself? That’s double standard!
你怎麼可以寬以律己、嚴以待人呢? 這樣是雙重標準!

4 . wound  創傷、傷口 

wound  [wund]  (n.)  創傷、傷口 (v.) 使受傷
I think my wound just got infected.
我認為我的傷口受感染了。

I think he was wounded by the sharp edges of the cart.
我認為他應該是被推車上尖銳的邊緣傷到了。

5 . emotional  情感上的 

emotional  [ɪˋmoʃən!]  (adj.)  情感上的、情緒化的
There is a saying that women tend to be more emotional while they're on their periods.
曾經有人這麼說，女生在月經來的時候可能會比較情緒化。

emotion  [ɪˋmoʃən]  (n.)  情感