1. 
a. incubator (n.)  孵化器、孕育地
b. incubate (v.)  孵卵、培養、醞釀
c. incubation (n.)  孵化、潛伏期
  -> incubation period 潛伏期
  -> The incubation period of AIDS 
      could be pretty long, so you 
      should still be careful.
     AIDS的潛伏期可以很長，所以
    你還是應該要小心。
2. 
a. dualistic (adj.)  二元的
  * 字首du：二
b. dual (adj.)  兩個的、成雙的
  -> Her dual rule as a representative 
      and the leader of the team, brings 
      her a great pressure.
    同時扮演隊伍發言人及領導人的
    雙重角色帶給她極大的壓力。
c. duplicate (adj.)  完全一樣的、複製的
d. duet (n.)  二重唱、二重奏
3. 
a. harsh (adj.)  嚴酷的、嚴厲的
b. severe (adj.)  嚴厲的、苛刻的
c. ruthless (adj.)  無情的、殘忍的
  * 較用來形容人的個性或他使用的手段
  -> According to the history records, 
      Adolf Hitler was ruthless to the 
     Jewish people and had commanded 
     his army to kill tons of them.
   根據歷史紀錄，希特勒對待猶太人十
   分殘忍，並曾命令軍隊屠殺他們。
4. 
a. simultaneously (adv.)  同時地
  * 注意"i"發音/aɪ/
b. simultaneous (adj.)  同步的、同時發生的
  -> Simultaneous interpreting is too 
      difficult for me, I don't think I can 
      react fast enough.
    同步口譯對我來說太難了，我不認為
    我能夠反應的這麼快。
--------------------------------------
London was becoming the incubator of the modern world through new patterns in industry, trade, and social mobility. Dickens's London is therefore a dualistic space: a harsh world that is simultaneously filled with wonder and possibility.

