1. 
a. imagine (v.)  想像
  -> Imagine if you were a millionaire, how awesome would life be!
    想像你是一個百萬富翁，那你的人生會過得多舒服啊！
b. image (n.)  映像，影像，圖像
  -> google image 用google找圖片
  -> The image links to our website.
    這張圖片有連結到我們的網站。
c. imagination (n.)  想像力；創造力
  -> Imagination is your superpower.
    想像力是你的超能力。
2. 
a. compliment (n.)  讚美的話，恭維
  -> Everyone likes to hear compliments. It makes people feel good about themselves.
    大家都喜歡聽到讚美的話，因為會讓他們感到很舒服。
b. complimentary (adj.)  免費的
  -> The tea and coffee are complimentary.
    這些茶和咖啡是免費的。
3. 
a. itch (v.)  發癢
  -> I remember having chicken pox when I was in second grades. Everywhere itched. It was terrible.
    我還記得我小學二年級時有得過水痘，全身都很癢，真是太痛苦了。
b. ache (v.)  疼痛
  -> My tooth is aching so badly, but I hate going to the dentist.
    我的牙真的很痛，可是我很討厭去看牙醫。
c. sore (n.)  痛處；痠痛
  -> My muscle is still sore from working out.
    我昨天健身，到現在肌肉都還感覺很痠痛。
4. 
a. annoying (adj.)  討厭的，惱人的
  -> My boyfriend is super annoying sometimes.
    我男朋友有時候真的非常煩人。
  -> It is so annoying the teacher keeps giving us homework.
    老師一直出作業給我們，好煩。
b. irritating (v.)  激怒，惱怒，生氣
  * 比annoying更激怒人
  -> Her little brother is quite irritating.
    他的弟弟真的很煩人。
c. provoking (adj.)  令人生氣的
  -> The Parkland shooting was very provoking and very upsetting.
    佛州的槍擊案真的很令人生氣及難過。
--------------------------------------
Just imagine, instead of being a stupid comment, a microaggression is a mosquito bite. Argh, It's a compliment! Mosquito bites and their itch are one of nature's most annoying features.