1. 
a. exude (v.)  明顯地流露、散發
  -> She just exudes confidence.
    她顯得信心十足。
b. express (v.)  表達、表示
  -> Artists often express themselves through their work.
    藝術家經常透過作品來表達自己。
c. expose (v.)  使暴露於、揭露
  -> Their scheme was exposed by the detectives.
    他們的陰謀被偵探們揭露了。
d. reveal (v.)  揭露、顯露
  -> He revealed the secret by accident.
    他不小心洩漏了這個秘密。
2. 
a. reaction (n.)  反應、回應
  -> I love to watch people's reactions when I say who I am.
    我喜歡觀察人們在聽到我說出我是誰之後的反應。
b. react (v.)  反映、回應
  -> How did she react to the news about her mother?
    她對於母親的消息反應如何。
c. reflection (n.)  反映、反射
  -> The man gazed at his reflection in the window.
    那個人盯著窗戶上的倒影看。
d. respond (v.)  回答、做出反應
  -> He responded "I don't know" to every question, which was very frustrating.
    每個問題他的回答都是我不知道，這令人非常挫折。
3. 
a. pack (n.)  一群、一隊；包裝、包裹
  -> a wolf pack 狼群
  -> a pack of wild dog 一群野狗
  -> a dog pack 一群狗
b. load (n.)  負擔、工作量
  -> I got a load/lot of work to get through tonight.
    今晚我要完成很多工作。
c. burden (n.)  負擔、沉重的責任
  -> the burden of responsibility 責任的重擔
  -> My elderly mother worries that she is a burden of my sibling and me.
    我年邁的母親擔心他會成為我和兄弟姐妹的負擔。
4. 
a. attention (n.)  注意、照顧
  -> Ladies and gentlemen. Could I have your attention, please?
    女士、先生們，請大家注意一下好嗎？
b. attend (v.)  出席、照顧
  -> He did not attend the meeting yesterday.
    他昨天沒有參加會議。
  -> attend to + sb/sth 照顧某人/處理某事
  -> Doctors tried to attend to the worst injured victim first.
    醫生們努力先救治受傷最嚴重的士兵。
c. attendance (n.)  出席、出席人數
  -> My attendance at school was always excellent.
    我在學校的出席情況一向都很好。
5. 
a. affection (n.)  喜愛、鍾愛
  -> He has a deep affection for his grandmother. 
    他非常喜歡他的奶奶。
b. affect (v.)  影響、使感動
  -> I was deeply affected by the novel.
    我被這本小說深深打動了。
c. effect (n.)  結果、作用、影響
  -> I tried taking some medicine to treat my headache, but it didn't have any effect.
    我試著吃了幾顆頭痛藥，但是這一點都沒有減輕我的頭痛。
  -> This had a great effect upon the future of both mother and son.
    這對母子倆的將來影響很大。
--------------------------------------
Dogs share 99% of their DNA with wolves. However, dogs exude a sense of warmness to other dogs and humans, unlike the wolf's reaction to others. Dogs are social pack animals who require attention and affection just like humans.