This combination of mucus, oil, skin cells and other debris in your eye serves as 
a protective shield and allows the eye to function properly. So let’s get technical for a second: 
the eyes of mammals are covered by a multi-layer film that helps them do what they’re supposed to do.

你眼睛中黏液、油酯、皮膚細胞和碎屑的混合物其實是個防護罩，讓我們的眼睛可以正常運作。技術上來說，
哺乳類的眼睛都有一個多層的薄膜來協助眼睛的運作。

1 . combination  結合(體) 

combination  [͵kɑmbəˋneʃən]  (n.)  結合(體) 
I’ve heard that Cirque du Soleil is doing a combination of gymnastics and Avatar.
太陽劇團最近傳出會做出結合體操以及阿凡達的表演。

combine  [kəmˋbaɪn]  (v.)  結合 
I’ve heard that if you combine fast noodles and cheese, it’s actually surprisingly delicious.
如果你結合泡麵和起司聽說它還滿好吃的。

2 . mucus  黏液 

mucus  [ˋmjukəs]  (n.)  黏液 

3 . debris  殘骸、瓦礫 

debris  [dəˋbri]  (n.)  殘骸、瓦礫 
They adopted a dog that was found in the debris of the collapse.
他們領養了一隻在建築物殘骸中找到的狗。

4 . shield  盾牌、保護者 

shield  [ˋʃild]  (n.)  盾牌、保護者 (v.) +from保護某人免於受到傷害
A home is a place that shields me from all of my sorrows.
家就是讓我可以不用感受到哀傷的地方。

5 . mammal  哺乳動物 

mammal  [ˋmæm]  (n.)  哺乳動物 

reptile  [ˈreptaɪl]  (n.)  爬蟲類 
lizard蜥蜴、crocodile/alligator鱷魚、tortoise/turtle烏龜