These obsessions are typically intertwined with compulsions — repeated actions. The person has to do just to function.
 If someone is obsessed with germs, they might wash their hands over and over, 
even after they logically know that they are clean.

而沉迷常與強迫交錯在一起 – 反覆採取行動，他常常只是為了做而做。如果某些人沉迷於消毒殺菌，他們會一遍又一遍地洗手，
即便他們理性地知道自己其實是乾淨的。

1 . obsession  著迷 

obsession  [əbˋsɛʃən]  (n.)  著迷 
His girl friend doesn’t approve his obsession with video games. 
他的女朋友對於他沉迷於打電動這件事情十分不能認同。

obsess  [əbˋsɛs]  (v.)  迷住 
He is obsessed with the Marvel series.
他對於整個漫威漫畫系列感到十分著迷。

2 . intertwine  糾結 

intertwine  [͵ɪntɚˋtwaɪn]  (n.)  糾結 
Since the day I met you, I feel like our lives are intertwined.
自從我認識你那天開始，我們的生命便完美地交錯在一起。

3 . compulsion  衝動 

compulsion  [kəmˋpʌlʃən]  (n.)  衝動 

compulsive  [kəmˋpʌlsɪv]  (adj.)  強迫的、衝動的(主動的)
compulsive shopping
衝動型消費

compulsory  [kəmˋpʌlsərɪ]  (adj.)  必須的(被動的)
This is a compulsory update.
這是要強迫更新的。

This course is compulsory.
這門課是你必須要修的。

4 . logically  邏輯上地 

logically  [ˋlɑdʒɪk!ɪ]  (adv.)  邏輯上地 
Even though logically I know he is right, I’m so mad at him.
儘管知道邏輯上他是對的，不過我還是很生氣。

logical  [ˋlɑdʒɪk!]  (adj.)  邏輯的 
I think he is being very logical here.
我認為他所說的事情都非常有邏輯。

logic  [ˋlɑdʒɪk]  (n.)  邏輯 
As a child, he loved solving logic puzzles.
在他小時候，非常喜歡這些邏輯的小謎題。