Hong Kong, being a former British colony, has long been dominated by Cantonese and English. 
However, in 2012, Mandarin narrowly overtook English as the second most commonly spoken language in Hong Kong, 
thanks to efforts by the Chinese Communist Party to spread Mandarin, especially in the education system.

至於前英國殖民地的香港長期以來都是以說粵語和英語為主。然而，到了 2012 年使用中文的族群才略微超過英語族群並成為
香港人第二常用的語言。這都要歸功於中共努力推行中文，特別是在教育制度中很強調這部分。

1 . former  從前的 

former  [ˋfɔrmɚ]  (adj.)  從前的 

latter  [ˋlætɚ]  (adj.)  後面的 
Deeply fried food and Sugary drinks are both really bad for your health; however, well, 
the former increases your body fat; the latter increases your aging speed.
油炸的食物與含糖的飲料都對我們的健康非常不好；前者會增加我們的體脂肪，後者會增加我們的老化速度。

2 . colony  殖民地 

colony  [ˋkɑlənɪ]  (n.)  殖民地 
India was once a British colony. 
印度曾是英國的殖民地。

colonial  [kəˋlonjəl]  (adj.)  殖民地的 
colonial ages 殖民時代

colonize  [ˋkɑlə͵naɪz]  (v.)  開拓為殖民地 
Macau was colonized by Portuguese a while ago.
澳門之前曾經被葡萄牙統治過。

Portuguese egg (custard) tarts
葡式蛋塔

colonization [͵kɑlənɪˋzeʃən] (n.) 殖民地的開拓，殖民；殖民地化[U]
the colonization of America by the British, Dutch and French
英國人、荷蘭人和法國人拓殖美洲

3 . dominate  主宰 

dominate  [ˋdɑmə͵net]  (v.)  主宰 
The society was dominated by males a few hundred years ago and right now, the time is about to change.
社會在幾百年前被男性主宰，現在時代也比較不一樣了。

domination  [͵dɑməˋneʃən]  (n.)  支配 
She has been under the domination of her father since childhood. 
她自孩提時代起一直受父親控制。

4 . education  教育 

education  [ɛdʒʊˋkeʃən]  (n.)  教育 
The government's policy on higher education is a success.
政府的高等教育政策很成功。

educate  [ˋɛdʒə͵ket]  (v.)  教育 
Kids often make mistakes in public, but I think they need to be educated right on the spot.
有時候小孩子會在公共場所犯錯，可是他們在當場是需要被教育的。