Hi guys, welcome to today’s pronunciation challenge and my name is Kristi. 
So, today, we have a video from the school primarily called the wisdom of animals. 
So if you guys have a pet, maybe a dog or a turtle or cats, you might have learned something from your pets 
because they’re so different from us and this video tells us why. So, let’s take a look at today’s sentences.

One of the most consoling aspects of animals – it might be a dog, a sheep, a lizard or a beetle – 
is that their priorities have nothing whatsoever to do with our own perilous and tortured agendas. 
They are redemptively unconcerned with everything we are and want.

動物們最撫慰人心的一點－不管是一隻狗，一頭羊，一隻蜥蜴或是一隻甲蟲－牠們優先考慮的事與我們可怕且折磨人的待辦事項完全無關。
對於我們是誰以及我們想要什麼也全然不在乎。

1 . console  安慰 

console  [kənˋsol]  (v.)  安慰 
She is just trying to console you and don’t try to push her away.
她只是想要安慰你而已，你沒有必要把她拒於千里之外。

console  [ˋkɑnsol]  (n.)  操縱台 (搖桿、面板)

2 . priority  優先順序 

priority  [praɪˋɔrətɪ]  (n.)  優先順序 
Get your priority straight! 搞清楚優先順序(可半開玩笑的講

Get your priority straight! What are you doing right now?
你要搞清楚優先順序好不好！你現在在做甚麼？(怎麼還在看影集呢？)

prioritize  [praɪˋɔrə͵taɪz]  (v.)  按優先順序處理 (你應該要把你應該要做的事情排好優先順序)
When you prioritize your To-Do List, it helps you get things done.
你如果先把你的代辦事項標清楚它的優先順序的話，能讓你更有效率地完成事情。

3 . perilous  冒險的 

perilous  [ˋpɛrələs]  (adj.)  冒險的 
The journey through the jungle was perilous. 
穿過叢林的旅行充滿了危險。

peril  [ˋpɛrəl]  (n.)  嚴重、危險 
Technology has enormous promise but also peril.
科技有絕佳的榮景，可是也有很大的危害。(隱藏著危機)

4 . redemptive  救贖的 

redemptive  [rɪˋdɛmptɪv]  (adj.)  救贖的 

redemption  [rɪˋdɛmpʃən]  (n.)  救贖 
Some people are seeking for redemption in their life.
有些人在他們一生當中其實是不斷地找尋他們的救贖。
*P的音很輕微，甚至可以用停頓代替它的位置