Poison vs. venom: What's the difference?
As it seeps into your skin and travels through your blood, the poison starts to interfere with your nerves, preventing your muscles form contracting.
seep [sip] v. 滲出 / n. 小泉;水路兩用吉普
When fear overcomes our minds, it begins to seep into our actions.
venom [ˋvɛnəm] n. 毒液；惡意 / v. 放毒
Snake venom solution immediately taking pills.
poison  [ˋpɔɪzn]  (n.)  毒藥、毒物
poison  [ˋpɔɪzn]  (v.)  下毒、污染
poisonous   [ˋpɔɪznəs]  (adj.)  有毒的、惡毒的

venom

combat poison with poison 以毒攻毒

food poisoning 食物中毒

poison gas 毒氣

poison-pen letter 惡意中傷的信


My mother put some rats' poison in the kitchen.
Can you tell the poisonous mushrooms from edible ones?

interfere  [͵ɪntɚˋfɪr]  (v.)  干預、打擾
intervene  [͵ɪntɚˋvin]  (v.)  干涉、阻礙
interact  [͵ɪntəˋrækt]  (v.)   互動
interrupt   [͵ɪntəˋrʌpt]  (v.)  打斷
interpret  [ɪnˋtɝprɪt]  (v.)  詮釋、口譯
intercept  [͵ɪntɚˋsɛpt]  ( v.)  攔截

interfere with

inter- 縱橫交錯的意思

intersection 交叉路口

interfering (adj.)愛管閒事的

interpreter


I don't want to interfere with him when he is working.
interfering adj. 愛管閒事的
You'd better not intervene in their dispute.
My favorate professor always interacted with students in class.
Sorry to interrupt, but you have a emergency call.
My literature professor ask us to interpret a point from Emily Dickinson.
We have to ask our tour guy to interpret for us.
interpreter n. 口譯員
Tons of drug are intercepted at customs.
I have to go home and intercept my report card before my mother does.

prevent   [prɪˋvɛnt]  (v.)  阻止、妨礙、預防
deter  [dɪˋtɝ]  (v.)  阻撓
hinder  [ˋhɪndɚ]  (v.)  妨礙
discourage  [dɪsˋkɝɪdʒ]  (v.)  使洩氣、潑冷水
dissuade  [dɪˋswed]  (v.)  勸阻

prevent from sth

deter from sth

hinder from sth

High prices are deterring young people from buying a house.
His criticism has discouraged him from writing another book.
My dad tried to dissuade me from living to a university far away from home.

