# Travel Frog
So this is the part of the core loop where you're gonna actually get presents back over the period of time. As you can see, he sent back 501 clovers, which is extremely nice of him.
core  [kor]  (adj.)  核心、重要
core curriculum [kor kəˋrɪkjələm] (n.)  基礎課程
The lack of government funding is at the core of problems.
loop  [lup]  (n.)  環狀物、圓圈
in a loop  (phr.)  迴圈
knock somebody for a loop  (phr.)  使大為驚訝
The tape ran in a continuous loop repeating the same songs over and over.
He knocked me for a loop when he said he was quitting his job.
present  [ˋprɛznt]  (n.)  禮物(gift)
present  [prɪˋzɛnt]  (v.)  贈送、呈現
I don't have her present address.
He had to present a smiling face though he was very worried.
period  [ˋpɪrɪəd]  (n.)  時期、月經
She is uncomfortable because she is on her period.
clover [ˋklovɚ] n. 三葉草, 紅花草，苜蓿
In many parts of the world clover is grown as food for cattle.
extremely  [ɪkˋstrimlɪ]  (adv.)  非常(very)
extreme  [ɪkˋstrim]  (adj.)  極端的、極惡劣的
I am extremely sorry.
Under extreme weather conditions, we can not go shipping.