On the contrary(放句首)

Tonal contrast色調對比

There is a huge contrast(很明顯的差別) between the two brothers.

The green mountains contrast against(對比) the blue sky.

Their stories contradicted(矛盾) each other. One of them must be lying.

How dare you contradict(頂撞、反駁) your father? 

The popular myth(一個普遍的迷思是) is that air travel is more dangerous than travel by car or bus.

The board game, travel frog, is gaining in popularity(人氣).

High population density(高人口密度)

Population growth.

China is the most populous country in the world.

Cold region 寒帶地區

Temperate and subtemperate regions.溫帶和亞溫帶

My friend is traveling to the great lakes' region(五大湖區) in America and she says, it's freezing right now.

Math really isn't my field(專長), you should ask Lily. 

I work in a company located in Xinyi district(Dist.).

Business district商業區

Residential zone住宅區

Elina studies abroad because she wanna get out of her comfort zone.

He's totally in my friend zone 他就完全只是我的朋友.

All areas of this country(全國各區) will have some rain tomorrow.