1. 
a. make sth. up  [mek ... ʌp]  (v.)  捏造
  -> This is a made-up story.
    這是一個捏造出來的故事。

b. invent  [ɪnˋvɛnt]  (v.)  捏造；虛構
  -> You invented that story just to sound cool, didn’t you?
    你捏造這個故事只是為了耍酷，對吧？

c. fabricate  [ˋfæbrɪ͵ket]  (v.)  偽造；杜撰
  -> These are fabricated events.
    這些是杜撰出來的事情。

2. 
a. anniversary  [͵ænəˋvɝsərɪ]  (n.)  週年紀念
  -> Oh my god! My husband forgot our anniversary.
    天阿！我老公忘了我們的結婚紀念日。

3. 
a. hand  [hænd]  (v.)  面交；傳遞
  -> Can you hand me that screwdriver?
    可以拿給我那個螺絲起子嗎？

b. give  [gɪv]  (v.)  給
  * 比較直接，相比之下有一點點不禮貌的感覺，不過日常使用沒關係
  -> Can you give me that bottle?
    可以給我那個瓶子嗎？

c. pass  [pæs]  (v.)  傳遞
  * 常用於用餐時
  -> Hey, can you pass me the salt?
    嘿，可以給我鹽巴罐嗎？

d. toss  [tɔs]  (v.)  丟；拋
  * 比較隨意的用法，可用在朋友之間
  -> Can you toss me that T-shirt?
    可以把那件T恤丟給我嗎？
-------------------------------------- 
Don't make stuff up. Nobody cares about your anniversary. The only anniversary I care about is the one where you're handing me a $20.