1. 
a. speak  [spik]  (v.)  說話，講話
  -> Action speaks louder than words.
    坐而言不如起而行。
  -> Could you speak up please? We can’t hear you in the back.
    可以請你講大聲一點嗎？坐在後面的人聽不到你講什麼。

b. speaker  [ˋspikɚ]  (n.)  說話者；演講者；演說家；
  -> The keynote speaker was really smooth.
    那個主講人講話很流暢。

c. speech  [spitʃ]  (n.)  演說，演講，致詞
  -> freedom of speech 言論自由
  -> Some said the lyrics of the song “This is America” is freedom of speech at its finest.
    有些人說”This is America” 這首歌的歌詞是言論自由最好的表現。

2.
a. yell  [jɛl]  (v.)  叫喊
  -> Stop yelling at me.
    不要再對我吼叫了。

b. hell  [hɛl]  (n.)  地獄
  -> If you tell on him, he will make your life a living hell.
    如果你告他的狀，他一定會讓你過的生不如死。

c. tell  [tɛl]  (v.)  告訴；講述；吩咐，命令
  -> Don’t tell me how to live my life.
    不要告訴我如何去過我的人生。

d. bell  [bɛl]  (n.)  鐘；鈴；門鈴；鐘聲；鈴聲
  -> The bell doesn’t dismiss you. I dismiss you.
    聽到鐘聲不代表你們可以下課，我說可以下課你們才可以下課。
  -> Doesn’t ring a bell.
    我想不起來。(當別人告訴你一件事情時。)

e. cell  [sɛl]  (n.)  細胞
  -> There won’t be any brain cells left after I finish these thesis.
    寫完這些論文之後我的腦細胞大概都會死光。

f. sell  [sɛl]  (v.)  賣
  -> He got caught for selling weed on campus.
    他因為在校園裡面販賣大麻而被警察逮補。

g. well  [wɛl]  (adj.)  健康的
  -> Hope you get well soon.
    希望你早日康復。

h. jello  [ˋdʒɛlo]  (n.)  果凍；食用凝膠及其製品
  -> Your tongue’s all green. How many of these jellos have you had?
    你的舌頭整個是綠色的，你到底吃了幾個果凍。

i. gel  [dʒɛl]  (n.)  膠體；凝膠
  -> hair gel 髮膠
  -> He uses way too much gel on his hair.
    他頭髮上面用太多髮膠了。

3.
a. time  [taɪm]  (n.)  時間；次；比賽暫停；刑期
  -> The clock’s ticking. We’re running out of time.
    時間一直在跑，我們快要沒時間了。
  -> perfect timing 時間算的很準
  -> time out 比賽暫停；你們都冷靜一下(用於有人在吵架時)
  -> We’ll let it slide this time. Don’t do it again.
    我們這一次放你一馬，不要再做了。
  -> Where did you do your time?
    你是在哪裡服刑期的？

4.
a. lesson  [ˋlɛsn]  (n.)  教訓；課程
  -> Lesson learned. When your girlfriend hit you when a single goodnight tags at 4 p.m. She’s low-key mad at you. If you say goodnight back, you’re dead meet.
    學到一課。如果你的女朋友在下午四點傳了”晚安”給你，就代表她在生你的氣。如果你這時候傳了”晚安”回去，你就死定了。
-------------------------------------- 
I think it speaks to all of us. It talks about how we all want to do what we want to do , right? We want to be ourselves. and we want to yell when we want to yell and play and laugh and have a good time. But as Mrs. Inkydink said, there's a time and a place for everything. And there is a time and a place to be considerate of other people's feelings. I think the lesson is: Be considerate.