1. 
a. part  [pɑrt]  (n.)  部分；部，篇；分冊，分輯；節，段；集；角色
  -> I don’t want to be a part of this.
    我不想牽扯這件事情。
  -> The Chinese part of me says, “Find a nice Chinese man to date.” The Japanese part of me says, “Find a nice Japanese man to date.” The American part of me advices, “I don’t know. They all look yellow to me.”
    我中國的一部分跟我說，找一個好的中國男生交往。我日本的一部份跟我說，找一個好的日本男生交往。我美國的一部份跟我說，我不知道，他們看起來全都黃黃的。(在開刻板印象的玩笑)
  -> I got a part in a movie.
    我得到了電影裡面的一個角色。
  -> Which part of the book are you on?
    那本書你讀到哪裡了？
  -> This is where we part ways.
   這是我們該分道揚鑣的時候了。

2. 
a. story  [ˋstorɪ]  (n.)  故事；傳聞；真相；情況
  -> His boss didn’t buy his story.
    他的上司不相信他說的話。

b. tale  [tel]  (n.)  故事，傳說；謊話，捏造的話
  -> fairytale 童話故事
  -> I read a bunch of fairytales growing up.
    我小時候讀了超多童話故事。

c. fable  [ˋfeb!]  (n.)  寓言
  -> A fable usually has a good lesson behind every story.
    寓言通常在每個故事中都會有一個很重要的教訓。

d. plot  [plɑt]  (n.)  （小說，戲劇等的）情節；密謀，策劃；(v.) 密謀，策劃
  -> She plots the whole thing herself.
   整件事情都是她自己策劃的。
  -> plot twist 劇情的扭轉、意想不到的大結局
  -> The music video of Freaky Friday has a great plot twist at the end.
    Freaky Friday這首歌的MV最後有一個很棒的劇情扭轉。

3.
a. work  [wɝk]  (n.)  工作；勞動；作業；事
  -> I’m buried in work. I need a drink after I close this case.
    我忙到不可開交，這個案子結束後我一定要去好好喝一杯。

b. job  [dʒɑb]  (n.)  工作；職業；零工
  -> I’m thinking about quitting my job for a change.
    為了做點改變，我在想要不要辭職。

c. career  [kəˋrɪr]  (n.)  職業
  * 指長期職業生涯
  -> career day 就業博覽會
  -> Some students find career day helpful, and some don’t.
    有些學生覺得就業博覽會很有幫助，有些覺得沒有。
  -> It’s harder to change your career path after your twenties.
    過了二十幾歲後，會更難去變換你的職業跑道。

4. 
a. hate  [het]  (v.)  仇恨，憎恨；嫌惡，不喜歡
  -> Oh~ I hate you.
    歐～我恨你。(有點朋友間開玩笑的成分在)
  -> I hate you. I love you. I hate that I love you.
    我討厭你，我喜歡你，我討厭自己喜歡你。(歌詞)

b. resent  [rɪˋzɛnt]  (v.)  憤慨；怨恨
  -> If you don’t let your son marry the girl he loves, he might spend the rest of his life resenting you.
    如果你不讓你的兒子跟他喜歡的女生結婚的話，他可能會花他的下半輩子來怨恨你。

c. despise  [dɪˋspaɪz]  (v.)  鄙視；看不起
  -> She despised the guy that asked for her number for looking poor, but she was all over him after she found out he’s rich. What a gold digger.
    這女生一開始因為那個男生看起來很窮而鄙視他，但他後來發現那個男生很有錢後就開始倒追他，真是一個拜金女。

I'm gonna make a part 2 and it's just gonna be stories about annoying customers that I had to deal with. And if anyone I used to work with is watching, and I didn't mention you, It's because I hate you.
第二集的主題會是我服務過的奧客。假如你和我工作過，但我沒有提到你，那是因為我討厭你！