1. 
a. condition  [kənˋdɪʃən]  (n.)  狀況；狀態；條件
  -> My mom still has our old bikes. They are very old, but they are in perfect condition.
    我媽還留著我們舊的腳踏車。雖然他們很舊，但狀況還是很好。

b. circumstance  [ˋsɝkəm͵stæns]  (n.)  情況；環境
  -> I think she was clam and coped very well under the circumstances.
    我覺得她在這個情況下很冷靜也處理得很好。

c. situation  [sɪtʃʊˋeʃən]  (n.)  處境；情況
  -> He is still positive while in a difficult situation.
    他即使在困難的處境下也保持樂觀。

2. 
a. over-the-counter  [oʊ.vɚ.ðəˈkaʊn.tɚ]  非處方的
  -> over-the-counter medicine 非處方藥、成藥
  -> There are many options for over-the-counter painkillers in the pharmacy.
    在藥局裡面有很多止痛成藥的選擇。

b. prescription  [prɪˋskrɪpʃən] (n.) 藥方、處方
  -> These drugs are only available through prescription. You can’t buy them over-the-counter.
    這些藥只能憑處方籤去購買，你不能買成藥。

3.
a. anti-inflammatory  [ˈænti-ɪnˈflæməˌtɔri]  (adj.)  抗炎的；消炎的
  -> Aspirin is an anti-inflammatory drug.
    阿斯匹林是一種消炎藥。

b. painkiller  [ˋpen͵kɪlɚ]  (n.)  止痛藥
  -> I need some painkillers for my headache.
    我需要一些止痛藥來減緩我的頭痛。

c. pill  [pɪl]  (n.)  藥丸（泛指所有的藥）

d. tablet  [ˋtæblɪt]  (n.)  藥片

e. capsule  [ˋkæps!]  (n.)  膠囊

4.
a. swelling  [ˋswɛlɪŋ]  (n.)  腫的地方；腫脹處
  -> Put your hand into cold water to help the swelling go down.
    把你的手泡到冰水裡可以減緩腫脹。

b. swell  [swɛl]  (v.)  腫脹；腫起
  -> His ankle began to swell after he sprain it.
    他扭到腳踝後，腳踝就開始腫脹了。
--------------------------------------
What can be done about these conditions, which dramatically affect many people’s quality of life? Tension headaches and most secondary cases can be treated with over-the-counter pain medications, such as anti-inflammatory drugs that reduce cranial swelling.