1. 
a. bet  [bɛt]  (v.)  打賭
  -> I bet… 我打賭... (通常口氣比較不屑)
  -> I bet you can’t handle 5 shots in a roll.
    我打賭你沒辦法連續喝五杯shots。
  -> Bet your bottom dollar that tomorrow there’ll be sun.
    跟你打包票，明日依舊是艷陽高照。

b. bat  [bæt]  (n.)  （棒球；板球的）球棒
  -> batting cage 打擊室
  -> The team is warming up in the batting cage.
    這個隊伍正在打擊室中熱身。

c. gamble  [ˋgæmb!]  (v.)  賭博；打賭
  -> Kristi gambled away their rent money.
    Kristi把他們的租金都打賭敗光了。

d. guess  [gɛs]  (v.)  猜測
  -> Take a wild guess.
    大膽猜看看。(通常魔術師請其他人猜測時會用)

2. 
a. chill  [tʃɪl]  (v.)  變冷，感到寒冷
  -> Chill out!
    冷靜下來！
  -> chills 雞皮疙瘩
  -> The music gave me chills.
    這個音樂好聽到讓我起雞皮疙瘩。
  -> I just chilling with my friends.
    我跟朋友一起放鬆。(=hanging)

b. chilly  [ˋtʃɪlɪ]  (adj.)  冷颼颼的
  -> The weather is quite chilly today.
    今天的天氣有點冷。

c. relax  [rɪˋlæks]  (v.)  放鬆
  -> Louis thinks mudding is relaxing.
    Louis覺得做泥浴很放鬆。
  -> chillax 冷靜、放鬆
  -> Dude. You need to chillax.
    哥們，你需要冷靜放鬆一下。

3. 
crack  [kræk]  (v.)  裂開，爆裂；破解（密碼）；(n.) 古柯鹼
  -> I can’t believe she cracked your code.
    我不敢相信她破解了你的密語。
  -> My screen cracked yesterday. If I take it to repair now, I’ll be broke for the rest of the month, and today’s only the first of May.
    昨天我的手機螢幕破了。如果我現在就拿去修，我接下來這個月就要沒錢了，而且今天才五月一號而已。
  -> The police broken to the house and they rested three people. They were busted with possession of three kilos of cracks.
    警方昨天闖入了這間民宅，並且逮捕了三個人。他們被發現擁有三公斤的古柯鹼。
  -> crack house 指房子裡的人有在使用毒品或販毒
  -> Michal Scott cracked a joke, but no one laughed.
    Michal Scott開了一個玩笑，但沒有任何人笑。
  -> He could crack open a safe and under two minutes.
    他可以在兩分鐘內破解一個保險箱。

4. 
a. intervention  [͵ɪntɚˋvɛnʃən]  (n.)  插入；介入；干預；調停
  -> intervene (v.) 干預
  -> smoking intervention 
  -> I wore a Halloween costume to a party at my friends, and it turned out to be an intervention for my drinking problem.
    我原本已經穿好萬聖節的服裝要去我朋友家的派對，結果發現那是為了勸戒我不要再喝酒的勸戒會。

b. meddle  [ˋmɛd!]  (v.)  干涉；管閒事
  -> Well… If you haven’t meddled to start with, then I wouldn’t have had to go in there and meddle myself. Now no matter how much we meddle, we’ll never be able to unmeddle the thing that you meddled up in the first place.
    如果你一開始沒有介入，那我就不需要介入，現在不管我們介入的多深，我們都沒辦法再回到最一開始你介入時的樣子。(unmeddle為口語的錯誤用法)
-------------------------------------- 
Well you done done me and you bet I felt it. I tried to be chill, but you're so hot that I melted. I fell right through the cracks, now I'm trying to get back. Before the cool done run out I'll be giving it my bestest. And nothing's going to stop me but divine intervention. I reckon it's again my turn to win some or learn some. But I won't hesitate no more, no more. It cannot wait, I'm yours.