1. 
a. meticulously  [məˋtɪkjələslɪ]  (adv.)  極注意地，極細心地
  -> She cleaned the house meticulously.
    她仔細的清掃了屋子。

b. meticulous  [məˋtɪkjələs]  (adj.)  過分精細的；小心翼翼的
  =careful =detailed
  -> She is a meticulous worker.
    她是一位做事非常仔細的員工。

c. careless  [ˋkɛrlɪs]  (adj.)  粗心的
  -> He got into an accident because of his careless driving.
  因為他粗心的駕駛，他發生了車禍。

2. 
a. map out  (phr.)  安排；詳細提出某事
  -> At our first group meeting, we mapped out our plan for the project.
    在我們首次團體會議中，我們詳細安排了我們的專案計畫。
  -> She has her entire future mapped out.
    她將她的未來詳細規劃好了。

b. plan out  為...作準備; 詳細安排
  = make a detailed plan
  = decide what you’re going to do in the future
  -> Before I go on a trip somewhere, I always plan out what I’m going to do there.
    在我出發前往任何地方旅遊之前，我都會詳細計畫我要在那裡做什麼。

3. 
a. devote  [dɪˋvot]  (v.)  將……奉獻（給），把…專用於
  -> The scientist devoted his life to researching cancer.
    這個科學家奉獻了他的一生來研究癌症。
  -> I devote most of my time to my work.
    我奉獻了我大部分的時間給我的工作。

b. devoted  [dɪˋvotɪd]  (adj.)  忠實的；摯愛的
  -> Susan has a very devoted husband.
    Susan擁有一位非常忠貞的先生。
  -> Maria is a devoted employee.
    Maria是一位非常忠誠的員工。

4. 
a. bug  [bʌg]  (v.)  在……安裝竊聽器
  -> Every room was bugged.
    每個房間都被安裝了竊聽器。
  -> The secret agent bugged the suspect.
    這個密探在嫌疑人身上安裝了竊聽器。
  -> The office was bugged.
    辦公室被安裝了竊聽器。
  -> The phones here are bugged.
    這裡的電話被安裝了竊聽器。

b. tap  [tæp]  (v.)  在……裝竊聽器
  -> The police tapped his phone.
    警方在他的電話中裝了竊聽器。

5.
a. overhear  [͵ovɚˋhɪr]  (v.)  無意中聽到；偷聽
  * 可能是無意或故意聽到
  -> I overheard their conversation when I passed by.
    我經過時不小心聽到了他們的對話。

b. eavesdrop  [ˋivz͵drɑp]  (v.)  竊聽
  * 故意偷聽
  -> My little brother eavesdropped on me and my friend.
   我的弟弟偷聽了我和朋友的對話。
--------------------------------------
Their days were meticulously mapped out, and any free time they had was devoted to honoring their Great Leader. Lesson plans had to meet the approval of North Korean staff, every class was recorded and reported on, every room was bugged, and every conversation, overheard.