1. 
a. unknowingly  [ʌnˋnoɪŋlɪ]  (adv.)  不知不覺地；無心地
  -> We’d often unknowingly wasted a lot of food.
    我們常常不知不覺地浪費了很多食物。

b. unknown  [ʌnˋnon]  (adj.)  不知道的；未知的；(n.) 未知的事物
  -> Her name is almost unknown a year ago, but now she is famous for her novel.
    她的名字在一年前還沒沒無聞，但現在卻因她的小說而聲名大噪。
  -> Many people fear the unknown.
    有很多人對於未知的事物感到害怕。

c. foreign  [ˋfɔrɪn]  (adj.)  外國的；陌生的；外來的
  -> The liquid is for flushing out the foreign object in the eyes.
    這個液體是用來沖出眼睛裡的異物的。

2. 
a. embarrass  [ɪmˋbærəs]  (v.)  使人不好意思
  -> Your inappropriate behavior embarrasses your family.
    你不合時宜的行為使你的家族蒙羞。

b. embarrassment  [ɪmˋbærəsmənt]  (n.)  窘迫；難堪
  -> Financial embarrassment made her sell the car.
    經濟困難使她不得不賣車。

c. dilemma  [dəˋlɛmə]  (n.)  困境，進退兩難
  -> She faces the dilemma for choosing her career path.
    她正面臨事業抉擇上的進退兩難。

3. 
a. norm  [nɔrm]  (n.)  基準；規範；常態
  -> Population aging is becoming a norm in developed countries.
    人口高齡化正在成為已開發國家的常態。

b. standard  [ˋstændɚd]  (n.)  標準；規格；規範
  -> My teacher said that my work wasn’t up to his standard.
    我的老師說我的功課沒有達到他的標準。

c. criterion  [kraɪˋtɪrɪən]  (n.)  標準，準則，尺
  -> 複數 criteria 
  -> The crowd wasn’t sure what criteria the judges used to select the contestants.
    觀眾們不清楚評審們是用什麼標準來選參賽者的。

4. 
a. observe  [əbˋzɝv]  (v.)  看到；觀察；奉行
  -> We observed the habitat of the reindeer carefully for a month, and found something strange.
    我們花一個月仔細觀察了迷路的棲息地，並且發現一些奇怪的地方。

b. note  [not]  (v.)  注意；記下
  -> I noted that he didn’t pay attention to the speaker. 
    我注意到他當時沒有專心聽講。

c. notice  [ˋnotɪs]  (v.)  注意，注意到
  -> My dog didn’t notice that I entered the room.
    我的狗沒有注意到我已經進房間了。

5. 
a. likewise  [ˋlaɪk͵waɪz]  (adv.)  同樣地
  -> It was nice to meet you. Likewise.
    很高興認識你。我也是。

b. as well  [æz wɛl]  同樣地
  = also 
  -> Just like my sister, I like spicy food as well.
    我跟我姊姊一樣都喜歡吃辣。

c. moreover  [morˋovɚ]  (adv.)  而且；再者；此外
  -> His essay didn’t meet the standards, moreover, some part of it are plagiarized. 
    他的論文沒有達到某些標準，甚至有些部分還是抄襲來的。
--------------------------------------
As a tourist, we can sometimes break those rules unknowingly and find ourselves embarrassed or even in serious legal trouble. So it is usually best to read up on the cultural norms, and if in doubt, look around and observe how the locals behave, and do likewise.