1. 
a. sarcasm  [ˋsɑrkæzm]  (n.)  諷刺
  * 重音在第一音節
  * 通常是貶義，或是取笑
  -> It is difficult to convey sarcasm through writing.
    透過寫作很難傳達諷刺意味。

b. sarcastic  [sɑrˋkæstɪk]  (adj.)  諷刺的
  * 重音在第二音節
  -> I was being sarcastic. How could you not tell?
    我正在諷刺，你怎麼會聽不懂？

c. irony  [ˋaɪrənɪ]  (n.)  反語；冷嘲
  * 重音在第一音節

d. ironic  [aɪˋrɑnɪk]  (adj.)  用反語的；冷嘲的
  * 重音在第二音節
  -> The man who invented the seat belt died in the car crash. That’s pretty ironic.
    發明安全帶的人在車禍死亡，真是諷刺。

2.
a. opposite  [ˋɑpəzɪt]  (adj.)  相反的
  -> Hot is the opposite of cold.
    熱是冷的相反。
  -> Big is the opposite of small.
    大是小的相反。

b. oppose  [əˋpoz]  (v.)  反對；反抗
  = be against sth.
  -> I oppose any laws that encourages discrimination.
    我反對任何鼓勵歧視的法律。

3.
a. confusing  [kənˋfjuzɪŋ]  (adj.)  令人困惑的

b. puzzling  [ˋpʌzlɪŋ]  (adj.)  令人困惑的
  * puzzle 拼圖
  -> The stories my father tells are often quite puzzling.
    (I was puzzled by his stories.)
    我的父親講的故事常常很令人困惑。

c. baffling  [ˋbæf!ɪŋ]  (adj.)  令人困惑的
  * 比confusing更困惑，完全搞不清狀況
  * sth. is baffling = sth. makes you baffled
  -> We all found this mystery quite baffling.
    我們都覺得這個謎題很令人困惑。
--------------------------------------
That was sarcasm. Sarcasm is where people say the opposite of what they mean, and they use it to talk about things they don't like - it can be confusing.

