Were Amazons merely figures of myth, or something more? It was long assumed that they were imaginary, like the cyclops and centaurs. But curiously enough, stories from ancient Egypt, Persia, the Middle East, Central Asia, India, and China also featured Amazon-like warrior women.

亞馬遜戰士只是神話人物嗎？ 還是並不只如此？長久以來，人們認為他們是想像出來的，就像獨眼巨人與人馬一樣。可讓人感到好奇的是， 古埃及、波斯、中東、中亞、印度以及中國的故事皆有提到像亞馬遜族的女戰士。


1. _
 * merely ['mɪrli] (adv.) 僅僅，不過
 - just, only
 - I wasn't mad. I merely get moody.
 + 我沒有生氣，只是心情不好。
 - I didn't say your fat. I merely suggested that you should not eat too much sugar.
 + 我沒說你的胖我只是建議你不要吃太多的糖。
 - Normal is merely average.
 + 正常只是平均水平。
 + => Meaning being a norm shouldn't be one's ultimate goal because by then you are no more than an average.
 * simply ['sɪmpli] (adv.) 僅僅，只不過；完全地
 - just, only
 - He doesn't like his job. He simply does it for the money.
 + 他不喜歡他的工作，他只是為了錢而做。
 - absolutely => 強調
 - It's simply beyond words.
 + 無法用語言描述。
 - You look simply stunning today.

2. _
 * assume [ə'sjum] (v.) 以為；（想當然地）認為
 - to accept something to be true without question or proof
 - We all know that life is short, but ironically we also assume that we still have time.
 + 我們都知道生命是短暫的，但具有諷刺意味的是，我們也認為我們還有時間。
 + ironically => 諷刺
 * assumption [ə'sʌmpʃən] (n.) 假設；臆斷
 - People tend to make assumptions about something.
 + 人們傾向於對某事做出假設。
 - People tend to make an assumption about a movie based on the title.
 - People tend to make an assumption about a book solely (based) on the book’s cover.
 - People tend to make an assumption that black people are automatically guilty. We must put that into stereotype(刻版印象）.
3. _
 * feature [fitʃɚ] (v.) 給予某人顯著地位；由某人擔任主角
 - to include someone or something as an important part
 - The film featured Gal Gadot debut as Wonder Woman princess of Amazon.
 + 這部電影的特色是Gal Gadot是亞馬遜的神奇女俠公主。
 * feature [fitʃɚ] (n.) 特色，特徵，特點
 - typical quality or an important part of something.
 - Natural feature.
 - Two of the most famous natural features in Taiwan are like Yehliu Park and Taroko Gorge.
 + 台灣最著名的兩個自然景觀就像野柳公園和太魯閣峽谷。
 - facial feature
 - Her eyes are her most distinct facial features.
 + 她的眼睛是她最明顯的面部特徵。
 - The song of the year goes to Telephone Lady Gaga featuring Beyonce.
 + 今年的歌曲是以Beyonce為特色的Telephone, Lady Gaga。
 + featuring => feat.