How do you pick what to watch? Is it a catchy title? Maybe an interesting synopsis? Perhaps it's the unwillingness to watch another episode of The Office... Or just maybe, a particular piece of cover art speaks to your spirit?

你是怎麼決定要挑哪部來看的呢？是根據吸睛的標題？是看到感興趣的影片簡介？還是逼不得已再繼續觀賞一集《我們的辦公室》(美國情境喜劇)？也可能是某部影片的主視覺設計讓你一見鍾情？

追劇：Binge-watching, binge-viewing or marathon-viewing.

cliffhanger(扣人心弦的故事、結局)

page-turner 引人入勝的書，令人愛不釋手的書

1. _
 * catchy ['kætʃi] (adj.) 動聽易記的；吸引注意的
 - it is used to describe something that is pleasing an easy to remember, especially for a song.
 - A catchy melody or a song with catchy lyrics.
 + 一首朗朗上口的旋律或一首歌詞。
 - something really catches our attention or interest
 - a catchy title, a catchy slogan, a catchy headline.
 - A five-word headline is often catchy and definitely gets right to the point.
 + 一個五個字的標題通常很吸引人，而且肯定是正確的。
 * eye-catching ['aɪ,kætʃɪŋ] (adj.) 引人注目的，搶眼的
 - It describes something so attractive and noticeable that can really catch your eyeball
 - To get you more thumbs up, you may need to stretch your creativity and use eye-catching headlines for your posts
 + 為了讓你獲得更多讚許，你可能需要擴展你的創造力並使用吸引人的頭條。

2. _
 * synopsis [sɪ'nɑpsɪs] (n.) （電影、書籍等的）概要，梗概
 - A brief description of the contents of a film or book.
 - Before I give you my review, I will give you a short synopsis of the plot.
 + 在我給你評論之前，我會給你一個簡短的情節概要。
 * trailer ['trelɚ] (n.) （影視節目、廣播的）預告片
 - it means an advertisement for a film or television.
 - HBO had just released the trailer for Game of Thrones season 8.
 + HBO發布了"Game of Thrones"第8季的預告片。
 * spoiler ['spɔɪlɚ] (n.) 破梗
 - it is referring to information about the plot that can spoil of your sense of surprise or suspense.
 - spoiler alert 防爆雷
 - I'm actually I don't know about you but I tend to avoid watching trailers. If I'm really going to enjoy the film because trailer is more less spoilers. Don't you think. Trailers are more less spoilers.

3. _
 * episode ['ɛpɪ,sod] (n.) （尤指電視或廣播節目的）一集
 - He just started his new career and it's now embarking on a new episode of his life.
 + 他開始了他的新職業生涯，現在開始了他生活中的新一頁。
 - Which episodes are you on? Which episodes are you watching right now?
 + 你現在在看哪集？
 * series ['siriz] (n.) （電視或廣播的）系列節目
 - I missed the second episode of the series.
 + 我錯過了系列的第二集。
 * season ['sizn] (n.) （電視系列節目）季
 - When will the new season of Game of Thrones be released?
 + "Game of Thrones"新一季何時會被釋放？