Hi guys, welcome today’s pronunciation challenge, and my name is Kristi. So today we have a video 
and it’s from BuzzFeedVideo: I Tried to Make Zero Trash for Thirty Days. So let’s take a look at today’s sentences.

We're stewards of this land, so every time we negatively impact the system, 
we're actually jeopardizing our ability to breathe, drink water, and consume food.

我們是土地的管理人，因此每一次我們負面影響這個系統，因此每一次我們負面影響這個系統，
我們其實就是在危害自己能夠呼吸，飲水，飲食的能力。

1 . steward  管家 

steward  [ˋstjuwɚd]  (n.)  管家 

2 . negatively  負面地、消極地 

negatively  [ˋnɛgətɪvlɪ]  (adv.)  負面地、消極地 

negative  [ˋnɛgətɪv]  (adj.)  負面的 
Negative emotions are often contagious.
負面的情緒通常都是有傳染力的。

negativity  [͵nɛgəˋtɪvətɪ]  (n.)  負面 
Sometimes, negativity can be processed through exercising.
有時候這些負面的感覺可以透過運動來消除。

positive  [ˋpɑzətɪv]  (adj.)  正面的 

positivity  [͵pɑzəˋtɪvətɪ]  (n.)  正面 
He shares his positivity through his speeches.
他透過他的演講來散播他的正向力。

3 . impact  衝擊 

impact  [ɪmˋpækt]  (v.)  (n.) 衝擊、影響
My teachers from my elementary school have a huge impact to me.
國小老師的言行對我有深遠的影響。

4 . jeopardize  危及 

jeopardize  [ˋdʒɛpɚd͵aɪz]  (v.)  危及 
By taking the risk, you are actually jeopardizing our business.
你冒這個險同時也危及了我們整個的企業。

jeopardy  [ˋdʒɛpɚdɪ]  (n.)  危險 
put something/someone in jeopardy
If your security check isn’t carried out thoroughly, the passengers’ life will be put in jeopardy.
如果安全檢查沒有詳細透徹的話，有可能危及到乘客的安全。

5 . consume  消耗 

consume  [kənˋsjum]  (v.)  消耗 
Swimming often consumes a lot of energy even more than jogging.
以同樣的距離來說，游泳消耗的體力比跑步還多。

consumer  [kənˋsjumɚ]  (n.)  消費者 
與customer不一樣
customer是客人；consumer泛稱所有的消費者

So, let’s take a look at our today’s sentences one more time.
We're stewards of this land, so every time we negatively impact the system,
 we're actually jeopardizing our ability to breathe, drink water, and consume food.

That’s for today’s pronunciation challenge. Please leave your recordings below, 
and I will challenge you guys tomorrow, bye!