After progressing this far, the immune system becomes suppressed is much more susceptible to cancers and 
opportunistic infections such as pneumonia. A person doesn't die from AIDS they actually die from an illness 
that the body could not fend off.

經過這段時間的發展，免疫系統受到抑制而容易罹患癌症和機會性感染如肺炎等，患者並不是死於愛滋病而是其他身體無法抵抗的疾病。

1 . immune  免疫的 

immune  [ɪˋmjun]  (adj.)  免疫的 
immune system 免疫系統

I am not immune to trypophobia.
我對於密集恐懼症無法免疫。(我非常怕群聚的東西。)

2 . suppress  鎮壓、壓抑 

suppress  [səˋprɛs]  (v.)  鎮壓、壓抑 
You should not suppress your feelings; you should try to let it out.
你不應該如此壓抑你的情緒；你應該試著將你的情緒抒發出來。

surpass  [sɚˋpæs]  (v.)  超過 
The outcome has surpassed the expected result.
這個結果已經超過能預期會有的結果。

3 . susceptible  易被影響的 

susceptible  [səˋsɛptəb!]  (adj.)  易被影響的 
The weather recently is susceptible to change.
最近的天氣是千變萬化的。

4 . fend  抵擋 

fend  [fɛnd]  (v.)  抵擋 (照顧自己沒有攻擊的動作)
He fended off a jab at his chest. 
他避開刺向胸口的一擊。

defend  [dɪˋfɛnd]  (v.)  防禦、捍衛 (為了保護自己而有攻擊的動作)
We shall defend our city, whatever the cost may be. 
不管代價如何，我們都要捍衛我們的城市。