domesticate  [dəˋmɛstə͵ket]  (v.)  馴養、馴化

domestic  [dəˋmɛstɪk]  (adj.)  家庭的、國內的
ex1. domestic violence 
家庭暴力
ex2. domestic flight
國內航班

species  [ˋspiʃiz]  (n.)  物種
ex. Human development has already put many species to (become) extinct.
人類開發已經讓很多物種都絕種了。

modify  [ˋmɑdə͵faɪ]  (v.)  更改
ex. Would you like to modify your order?
你會想要更改你的訂單嗎？

modification [͵mɑdəfəˋkeʃən]  (n.)  修改
ex. Few modifications should be made before we published this item.
在我們發表這個物品之前應該還要做一些修改。

intervention  [͵ɪntɚˋvɛnʃən]  (n.)  插手、介入
ex. 
intervene  [ɪntɚˋvin]  (v.)   干涉
ex. Interpol may seem like a great organization to remain world peace 
but most countries wouldn’t like other people to intervene with domestic affairs.
雖然國際刑警組織看似一個維持世界和平的組織，但是大部份的國家都不喜歡外界去干涉國內的事情。
*International Criminal Police Organization＝Interpol＝ICPO：國際刑警組織