measure  [ˋmɛʒɚ]  (v.)  測量、計畫
“ season of love ” 
ex. How do you measure a year?
你怎麼計算一整年的時間？
ans. Five hundred twenty five thousand six hundred minutes.
525,600 分鐘。

digestibility  [də͵dʒɛstəˋbɪlətɪ]  (n.)  可消化性
＊不常使用

digest  [daɪˋdʒɛst]  (v.)  消化
ex. Some hard of fruits like guava are harder to digest.
有些較硬的水果像是芭樂是比較難消化。

availability  [ə͵veləˋbɪlətɪ]  (n.)  有效
ex. You must check that the availability of your card before using it.
你在使用卡之前必須要確定卡是有效。

available  [əˋveləb!]  (adj.)  可用的
ex. We have eight toilets available on this airplane.
這個飛機上有八間廁所能使用。

amount  [əˋmaʊnt]  (n.)  總數、總額
＊the amount of Sth    ＸＸＸ的總額（數）

ex. We are currently calculating the amount of money that has been donated.
我們目前正在計算被捐款的總額。