Hi guys, welcome to today’s pronunciation challenge and my name is Kristi. 
So today, we have a video and it’s called Why We Love Repetition in Music. 
So if you guys have known this a lot of pop music has a huge relevance of a repetition, 
it means we have a repeated part, maybe it’s a chorus in a song. So let’s take a look at today’s sentences.
嗨大家好，歡迎來到今天的口說挑戰，我是Kristi。今天的影片是為什麼我們喜歡重複的音樂。
如果你們了解有很多的流行音樂與重複的樂句有很大的關連性，它代表在我們所熟知的音樂中帶有重複的樂句，也許是一首歌的副歌。
讓我們來看看今天的文章吧。
So, why does music rely so heavily on repetition? One part of the answer comes from 
what psychologists call the mere-exposure effect. In short, people tend to prefer things they've been exposed to before.

為什麼音樂如此仰賴重複性？一部分原因來自心理學家所謂的「單純曝光效應」。簡而言之，人們通常比較喜歡他們接觸過、熟悉的東西。

1 . rely  依靠、仰賴 

rely  [rɪˋlaɪ]  (v.)  依靠、仰賴 
A rely on B
   A 依靠於 B

The quality of a bowl of beef noodles heavily relies on its broth.
一碗牛肉麵的好壞取決於它的湯。

reliable  [rɪˋlaɪəb!]  (adj.)  可信賴的 
He is the most reliable man in this company.
他是公司內最值得信賴的人。

relay  [rɪˋle]  (n.)  接替、接力 
relay race 接力賽
swimming relay 游泳接力
jogging relay 跑步接力

2 . repetition  重複 

repetition  [rɛpɪˋtɪʃən]  (n.)  重複 

repeat  [rɪˋpit]  (v.)  重複 
Could you repeat that on more time, please? I didn’t get it.
你可以再重複一次嗎？我沒有聽懂你剛剛說甚麼。

3 . exposure  暴露 

exposure  [ɪkˋspoʒɚ]  (n.)  暴露 
Most celebrities prevent their child from the exposure in the media.
很多明星都會刻意避免自己的小孩在媒體中有太多的曝光。

expose  [ɪkˋspoz]  (v.)  使暴露於 
Vampires cannot be exposed in the sun.
吸血鬼大部分都不能暴露於太陽底下。

4 . prefer  寧可 

prefer  [prɪˋfɝ]  (v.)  寧可 
Which one do you prefer, tomato soup or clam chowder?
你比較喜歡哪一種？番茄湯還是蛤蠣濃湯？

preference  [ˋprɛfərəns]  (n.)  喜愛 

preferably  [ˋprɛfərəblɪ]  (adv.)  寧可、用…會比較好
If an agreement is made, there should be a contract preferably in written text.
用定型化契約完成協議會比較好。