The other option is co-producing the movie with a Chinese company so that it's not technically a foreign film. 
But co-productions are the most tightly regulated, with strict guidelines on things like the film's shooting location 
and its finances. It also has to have at least ⅓ of cast be Chinese. In short, China somehow has to play a significant role 
in the film, and it can't be as the villain!

另一個選擇是與中國公司一起合作製片，讓這部電影在技術上不會被歸類為「外國片」。但是共同製片的規範非常嚴苛，
涵蓋了拍攝地點及財務分配等等；中國演員的配置也必須至少佔有三分之一。簡而言之，
中國在電影中需要扮演著舉足輕重的角色—而且還不能是壞人！

1 . option  選擇 

option  [ˋɑpʃən]  (n.)  選擇 
You have two options here; you can choose to stay or leave.

optional  [ˋɑpʃən!]  (adj.)  隨意的 
In some airlines, meals are optional.

mandatory  [ˋmændə͵torɪ]  (adj.)  義務的 
The orientation is mandatory. Please be here at 10 a.m. sharp.

2 . foreign  外國的 

foreign  [ˋfɔrɪn]  (adj.)  外國的 

foreigner [ˋfɔrɪnɚ] (n.) 外國人
He is a foreigner.

domestic [dəˋmɛstɪk] (adj.) 國家的、國內的
domestic flight 國內班機
domestic violence 家庭暴力

3 . guideline  指導方針 

guideline  [ˋgaɪd͵laɪn]  (n.)  指導方針 
If you wish to stay, you should follow the guideline.

guide  [gaɪd]  (n.)  嚮導 
guide dog 導盲犬

guide [gaɪd] (v.) 引導
He is guiding me through the hardest time in life.

guidance  [ˋgaɪdns]  (n.)  引導 
Without the professor’s guidance, I wouldn’t have finished my dissertation.

4 . significant  有意義的 

significant  [sɪgˋnɪfəkənt]  (adj.)  有意義的 

significance  [sɪgˋnɪfəkəns]  (n.)  重要性 
This necklace stands for much significance for me since it’s a present from my mom.