And this basic finding, by the way, has been extended to other contexts, everything from chess to basketball, 
to computer programming and to dance. We store information in terms of meaning and not limited to particular sensory modes.

這項基本發現，順帶一提，已經有許多相關的延伸研究：概括了棋藝、籃球、電腦程式、甚至是跳舞。我們儲存資訊是依照其意義，而非自我的感官。

1 . extend  延長、延伸 

extend  [ɪkˋstɛnd]  (v.)  延長、延伸(上下)
Extend your arms and legs until you feel like you're touching the sky.

The application deadline has been extended.

extension  [ɪkˋstɛnʃən]  (n.)  伸展、延期、接髮
extension

expand  [ɪkˋspænd]  (v.)  擴張(左右)
This chain store is expanding fastly all over the country.

expansion  [ɪkˋspænʃən]  (n.)  擴展 
expansion pack

2 . context  文章脈絡 

context  [ˋkɑntɛkst]  (n.)  文章脈絡 
When you are writing an essay, make sure your context is coherent.

contextual  [kənˋtɛkstʃʊəl]  (adj.)  上下文的 

3 . limit  界線 

limit  [ˋlɪmɪt]  (n.)  界線 
The sky is the limit.

limit  [ˋlɪmɪt] (v.) 限制
My parents never limit what I want to do.

unlimited  [ʌnˋlɪmɪtɪd]  (adj.)  無限制的 
Once you become a member, you'll have unlimited access to all the online resources.

4 . particular  特殊的 

particular  [pɚˋtɪkjəlɚ]  (adj.)  特殊的 
He has a particular request about the wrapping of the package.

peculiar   [pɪˋkjuljɚ]  (adj.)  奇怪的 
There is something peculiar about his story, but I can’t name it.

5 . sensory  知覺的 

sensory  [ˋsɛnsərɪ]  (adj.)  知覺的 
A cat’s sensory organs are so much sharper than human’s.

sense  [sɛns]  (n.)  感官 

sense  [sɛns]  (v.) 感覺
I think he is sensing something unusual in his house