1-1. inability  [ɪnəˋbɪlətɪ]  (n.)  無能
e.g. Your inability to make smart decisions will result in failing this company.

1-2. ability  [əˋbɪlətɪ]  (n.)  能力、能耐  
e.g. He has an ability to read animal's minds.
-----

2-1. maintain  [menˋten]  (v.)  維持=to continue to have; to keep in existence, or not allow to become less(有修復而保持原狀之意)
e.g. I can't believe the roller coaster is maintaining and we have to miss the ride today.

cf. remain=to stay in the same place or in the same condition.(保持一樣,意即自始至終相同)
e.g. Even though we have gone on separate ways, our hearts remain the same.

2-2. maintenance   [ˋmentənəns]  (n.)  維持、保持
e.g. We have to call the mantenance(維修工,維修部門) to fix this problem.
-----

3-1. constant  [ˋkɑnstənt]  (adj.)  固定的=staying the same, or not getting less or more.
e.g. This plant requires constant and massive watering.

3-2. constantly  [ˋkɑnstəntlɪ]  (adv.)  不斷地
e.g. He's constantly complaining about his current job and is wishing to quit.

3-3. consecutive  [kənˋsɛkjʊtɪv]  (adj.)  連續不斷的=Consecutive events, numbers, etc. follow one after another without an interruption.
cf. constant (表頻率)連續不斷的=happening a lot or all the time
-----

4-1. accelerate  [ækˋsɛlə͵ret]  (v.)  加速
e.g. The latest model of the car can accelerate in just a few seconds.

4-2. acceleration  [æk͵sɛləˋreʃən]  (n.)  加速
-----

5-1. eventual  [ɪˋvɛntʃʊəl]  (adj.)  最終  <念這字要笑出來,原因不明^^)

5-2. eventually  [ɪˋvɛntʃʊəlɪ]  (adv.)  最後(有遲早都得遇到,最後都會發生之意)
e.g. You can avoid this problem as much as you want, but you're eventually gonna have to face it.

cf. finally=after a long time or some difficulty. (事物的最後)