She was this feisty young woman who spoke her mind, and had all of these ambitions, and was incredibly independent, 
and wanted to see the world, and was so smart. And I loved how she had this relationship with Beast
where they were just toe-to-toe. And… That to me just seemed like such a dynamic and interesting kind of relationship 
that I’d never seen before in a fairytale.

她是一位充滿魅力的年輕女性，她擅於表達內心的想法、滿懷野心、非常地獨立，想看看這世界，而且很聰明。
我也很喜歡她和野獸之間很密切的關係。這對我來說是一段充滿活力且有趣的關係，且在其他童話中前所未見。

1 . feisty  活躍的 

feisty  [ˋfaɪstɪ]  (adj.)  活躍的 
Belle was such a feisty young woman.

2 . ambition  雄心、抱負 

ambition  [æmˋbɪʃən]  (n.)  雄心、抱負 
One of his ambitions is to become the CEO of this company.

ambitious  [æmˋbɪʃəs]  (adj.)  富有野心的 
The rookie was somehow very ambitious.

3 . independent  獨立的 

independent  [independent]  (adj.)  獨立的 
financially independent 經濟獨立
When a child is financially independent, they would barely need support from their families.

dependent  [dɪˋpɛndənt]  (adj.)  依靠的 
He is very dependent on his mother.

depend  [dɪˋpɛnd]  (v.)  相信、信賴 
depend on 取決於
The result of this competition depends much on the judges.

4 . dynamic  生氣勃勃的 

dynamic  [daɪˋnæmɪk]  (adj.)  生氣勃勃的 
What I love about this campus is how dynamic it is!

5 . fairytale  童話故事 

fairytale  [ˋfɛrɪ͵tel]  (n.)  童話故事 
This is not a fairytale; this is reality!