Similar camps exist in the United States. But in general, gay conversion in the US is far less severe. 
It usually involves comprehensive talk therapy, seminars, weekend retreats or rehabilitation, 
and typically does not involve inhumane medical procedures. 

美國也有類似的矯正營，但是手段較不激進。包含談話治療、研商、週末休憩或復健，且通常不會採取不人道的醫學手段。

1 . exist  存在 

exist  [ɪgˋzɪst]  (v.)  存在 
That word doesn't exist in English. 
英語中沒有這個字。

existence [ɪgˋzɪstəns] (n.) 存在
With thought of having an alien exist, it really frightens me.
一想到外星人真實存在，實在令人感到恐慌。

2 . conversion  改變、轉變 

conversion  [kənˋvɝʃən]  (n.)  改變、轉變 
Conversion of your heating system from coal to gas will be costly. 
你把暖氣系統由燒煤改造成燒瓦斯會花好多錢。

convert  [kənˋvɝt]  (v.)  轉變、變換 
He has converted from an atheist to a Christian.
他從一個無神論者轉變成一個基督徒。

3 . severe  嚴重的 

severe  [səˋvɪr]  (adj.)  嚴重的 
The wound seems quite severe. I think you really need to call an ambulance.
我認為你的傷口看起來蠻嚴重的。可能需要叫一輛救護車。

4 . comprehensive  廣泛的 

comprehensive  [͵kɑmprɪˋhɛnsɪv]  (adj.)  廣泛的、綜合的
a comprehensive survey 全面的考察

comprehend  [kɑmprɪˋhɛnd]  (v.)  理解 
The child couldn't comprehend the text. 
這孩子不懂該課文的含義。

comprehension [͵kɑmprɪˋhɛnʃən] (n.) 理解、理解力
reading comprehension英文理解題

5 . rehabilitation  修復 

rehabilitation  [͵rihə͵bɪləˋteʃən]  (n.)  修復 
rehab 復健、勒戒
a rehabilitation center for drug addicts 吸毒人員康復中心

* She went into rehab for three years

6 . inhumane  殘忍的 

inhumane  [ɪnhjuˋmen]  (adj.)  殘忍的 
He received all kinds of inhumane treatment during his three-month stay in prison. 他在監獄裡待了三個月，受盡了不人道的待遇。

humane  [hjuˋmen]  (adj.)  有人情味的 
He's one of the most humane people I have ever worked with. 
他是與我一起工作過的人中最有人情味的一個。

humanity  [hjuˋmænətɪ]  (n.)  人道 
He treated the prisoners with humanity. 
他人道地對待俘虜。