You are not a failure. That tension is a really good thing, so embrace that drive that you have, 
embrace your ambition, and the gap between where you are and who you are today and where you want to go 
and who you want to become over the next year and ten years and so on.

你並未失敗。那種緊繃感是一件好事，所以，去接受、控制你所擁有的；去接受你的野心和你現在所處的位置、你現在是什麼樣的人，
以及你在明年、未來十年後所想要成為的人的差距。

1 . failure  失敗 

failure  [ˋfeljɚ]  (n.)  失敗 
Failure isn't a bad thing because at least you would know that you have tried.

fail  [fel]  (v.)  不及格、失敗 
When you consider yourself failed, you should think about why you have failed instead of being stuck in that negative emotion.

2 . tension  緊繃 

tension  [ˋtɛnʃən]  (n.)  緊繃 
You can feel the tension start to heating up in the room when they started to quarrel.

tense  [tɛns]  (adj.)  緊繃的 
I feel like your shoulders are a little bit tense, I think you really need a massage.

3 . embrace  擁抱 

embrace  [ɪmˋbres]  (v.)  擁抱 
They embrace each other and bid farewell.

After my persuasion, she finally embraced the idea that moving might be a good choice.

4 . ambition  雄心、抱負 

ambition  [æmˋbɪʃən]  (n.)  雄心、抱負 
One of his ambitions is to become a pilot in the future.

ambitious  [æmˋbɪʃəs]  (adj.)  有野心的 
Almost everyone in the office can tell that he is a little bit too ambitious.

5 . gap  分歧、隔閡 

gap  [gæp]  (n.)  分歧、隔閡 
I think there is a huge gap between my definition of successful and yours.

Generation gap occurs because either the kid or the parent refuses to communicate.