I'm a big believer in the idea that so many people make mistakes, and it's not the mistake that ruins them, it's the way they react to their mistake that ruins them.

--------------------------------------------------

1 . believer  信徒、信教者
believer  [bɪˋlivɚ]  (n.)  信徒、信教者
＊I'm a big believer that everyone should be equal.
＊I'm a big believer in the idea that we should live every single day like as our last day, and not put things off into the future.

believe  [bɪˋliv]  (v.)  相信、信任
＊I believe that ...

2 . mistake  誤解
mistake  [mɪˋstek]  (n.)  誤解
＊make a mistake
＊I broke the mirror by mistake. = I broke the mirror accidentally.

screw-up  [ˋskru͵ʌp]  (n.)  弄壞的事、犯錯誤的人 (非正式北美用法）
＊It's quite a bad screw-up.
＊I'm such a screw-up. = I screw everything up.

screw up  [ˋskru͵ʌp]  (v.)  搞糟、毀壞
＊You screw sth up. - You mess sth up.
＊Don't give it to him. He'll screw it up for sure.

3 . ruin  毀滅 ▲注意發音▲
ruin  [ˋrʊɪn]  (v.)  毀滅
＊He knocked the painting off the wall and completely ruined it.

destroy  [dɪˋstrɔɪ]  (v.)  毀壞、破壞
＊Don't let it ruin/destroy you.

4 . react  作出反應、反應
react  [rɪˋækt]  (v.)  作出反應、反應
＊react to sth = handle sth

handle  [ˋhænd!]  (v.)  對待、處理
＊misshandle  錯誤地處理；亂弄

5. It's quite well put.

6 . in no time 
in no time 很快
＊The doctor told him that he would get well again in no time. 醫生對他說, 他很快就會康復。
