It's frequently the case that new drugs, which work on these lab-grown cells, will fail in clinical trials with real patients. One of the complexities of aggressive tumors is that they can have multiple populations of slightly different cancerous cells.

常有的是，新藥能作用在實驗室培養出的細胞，卻在人體測試階段時失去效用。惡性腫瘤的複雜性在於它能分裂出許多有些微差異的癌細胞群。

筆記~有錯跟我說哦~

1. frequently  [ˋfrikwəntlɪ]  (adv.)  頻繁地
He is frequently making excuses for his own fault.
他很常為了他自己的過錯找藉口

frequent  [ˋfrikwənt]  (adj.)  時常發生的
frequent flyer 常坐飛機的客人，累積里程數

2. fail  [fel]  (v.)  不及格
He wanna pursue the girl but he failed miserably.
他想要追那個女生，但他失敗的很徹底

failure  [ˋfeljɚ]  (n.)  失敗
He's completely failure.
他完完全全地失敗

3. complexity  [kəmˋplɛksətɪ]  (n.)  複雜性
He wasn't able to solve the quiz immediately due to the complexity of the problem.
因為這個題目太過複雜了，以至於他無法馬上解出來

complex  [ˋkɑmplɛks]  (adj.)  複雜的
The relationship between characters in Game of Thrones is quite complex.
權力遊戲裡角色之間的關係其實是非常複雜的

4. aggressive  [əˋgrɛsɪv]  (adj.)  侵略的、侵犯的
She is quite aggressive when it comes to salary.
當提到薪水的時候，她會變得比較有侵略性，比較會捍衛自己

Thanks for reading and listening. Keep yourself warm.
Stay awesome. Peace! Bye.