Hi guys, welcome to today’s pronunciation challenge and my name is Kristi. So today we have a video from the school of life. Let’s go how to get over rejection. Being rejected can be a very sad thing and life and in this video teaches us how to get over it and you know, move on with life. So, let’s look at today’s sentences.
嗨大家好，歡迎來到今天的口說挑戰，我是主持人Kristi。今天我們的影片來自於生活中的學校。讓我們看看如何克服被拒絕的障礙。被拒絕這件事可以說是非常悲慘的事情與生活，而在這部影片中教導了我們如何克服它，然後你知道的，繼續過生活。讓我們看看今天的句子。

The true challenge is to stop being so revolted by people who do in fact want us and so admiring of those who don't. Think back to when you rejected people, you didn't hate them or regret them. The chief emotions are embarrassment and pity.
最大的挑戰是不要拒絕喜歡我們的人於千里之外，以及讚美那些不愛我們的人。回想一下，當你們拒絕別人時，你們不是討厭他們或是感到抱歉；最先感受到的是難堪和遺憾。

1 . revolt  反叛、起義 

revolt  [rɪˋvolt]  (v.)  反叛、起義 (很反對的意思)
revolted [rɪˋvoltɪd] (adj.) 很反感的
If your pick-up lines suck, girls can be quite revolted.
如果男生要搭訕別人的時候，講的話無法引起別人的興趣時，是會引起女生反感的。

2 . admire  欽佩、讚賞 

admire  [ədˋmaɪr]  (v.)  欽佩、讚賞 
I really admire his attitude toward work.
我對於他的工作態度真的感到很欽佩。

admirer  [ədˋmaɪrɚ]  (n.)  仰慕者 

3 . reject  拒絕 

reject  [rɪˋdʒɛkt]  (v.)  拒絕 
除了人與人之間會拒絕別人之外，學校或是工作的offer，如果沒有被錄取的話，也可以說with rejected，就是被拒絕。

eject  [ɪˋdʒɛkt]  (v.)  吐出、退出 
之前在用CD、DVD player或者甚至最早的錄音機上，將CD或是錄音帶退出的按鍵稱之為eject。

4 . regret  懊悔 

regret  [rɪˋgrɛt]  (n.) (v.) 懊悔 
regret + V-ing
I really regret staying up so late.
我真的很後悔前一天這麼晚睡。

I look back in regret.
我對過去感到懊悔。

5 . pity  憐憫、同情 

pity  [ˋpɪtɪ]  (n.) (v.) 憐憫、同情 (上對下的感覺)
平常並不會這樣用。

pitiful  [ˋpɪtɪfəl]  (adj.)  令人同情的 
Her situation after the flood is quite pitiful.
他因為那個洪水所帶來的災難，他現在的情況是滿令人同情的。