Hi guys, welcome to today’s pronunciation challenge and my name is Kristi. Have you had a nightmare before? It could be about a public speaking or could be about a zombie of apocalypse. But, today we have a video that’s called the good side of bad dreams, the science of us, so this video talks about how bad dreams are actually good for us. So, let’s take a look at today’s sentences.
嗨大家好，歡迎來到今天的口說挑戰，我是今天的主持人Kristi。你是否曾經有過惡夢呢？這個惡夢有可能是面對群眾的公開演講或者有可能是公園裡的葉子所形成的殭屍。但是今天我們的影片主題是惡夢的好處，人體的科學。這部影片提到惡夢為什麼對我們有實際上的好處。讓我們來看看今天的句子吧。

Research shows that the things that concern us most while we are awake continue to mess with us when we sleep. Your unconscious brain takes your abstract fears and turns them into stories
研究顯示，清醒時我們最擔心的事情會持續在睡夢中纏著我們。你沒有意識的大腦會將你抽象的恐懼轉化成故事，變成你的惡夢。

1 . concern  擔憂、關於 

concern  [kənˋsɝn]  (v.)  擔憂、(n.) 擔憂的事、關於 
That’s none of your concern!
這不關你的事！

I’m not concerned about missing a plane but losing our luggage.
我擔憂的事情不是我們會趕不上飛機而是會找不回行李。

2 . mess  一團亂 

mess  [mɛs]  (n.)  一團亂 
I am a mess right now.
我的人生現在好像一團亂。

messy [ˋmɛsɪ] (adj.) 雜亂的
His room is always so messy.
他的房間好像總是一團亂。

mass  [mæs]  (n.)  質量 

3 . unconscious  不省人事的 

unconscious  [ʌnˋkɑnʃəs]  (adj.)  不省人事的 

conscious  [ˋkɑnʃəs]  (adj.)  神智清醒的 
His condition has been stable right now and he is currently conscious.
他的情況大致穩定下來，然後現在也還算清醒。

4 . abstract  抽象的 

abstract  [ˋæbstrækt]  (adj.)  抽象的、(n.) 摘要
除了抽象的，我們有時候也會看到摘要，abstract也用到這個字，比如說論文最前面會有一個abstract，那它為什麼會當摘要呢？其實就是說，給大家一個抽象的概念說你這個論文大致是要寫些甚麼東西，所以也叫做abstract。