Hi guys, welcome to today’s pronunciation challenge and my name is Kristi. So today, we have a video which is a very, very important video if you love shopping because it’s called how to live a hundred. You might think what does shopping have to do, you know, with a longer life. That’s what I thought and that’s why it is important for those who love to shop. So, let’s look at today’s sentences.
嗨大家好，歡迎來到今天的口說挑戰，我是今天的主持人Kristi。今天我們的影片是一部相當重要的影片如果你喜愛逛街的話，因為這部影片被稱之為如何活到一百歲。你可能會認為逛街跟長壽到底有甚麼關聯呢？那就是我看到標題的想法以及為什麼對於喜愛逛街的人是一個重要的訊息。讓我們看看今天的句子。

The world health organization recommends at least 150 minutes per week of exercise, potentially adding 4 years to your life. This could be either swimming or even... shopping? A Taiwanese study found that those who shop daily, even if they didn't buy anything, lowered their risk of death by 23% to 28%.
世界衛生組織建議人們至少一週運動150分鐘，這麼做可能多增加四年的壽命，例如去游泳，甚至是......逛街購物？一個台灣的研究指出每日皆去購物者，即使他們並未購買任何商品，也會讓死亡率降低23%至28%。

1 . organization  組織、團體 

organization  [ɔrgənəˋzeʃən]  (n.)  組織、團體 
WHO: world health organization世界衛生組織

WTO: world trade organization世界貿易組織

organizer  [ˋɔrgə͵naɪzɚ]  (n.)  組織者 
As an event organizer, it is your responsibility to make sure everything runs smoothly.
身為一個活動的組織者，你必須確保每個活動之間順利地進行。

2 . potentially  可能地 

potentially  [pəˋtɛnʃəlɪ]  (adv.)  可能地 

potential  [pəˋtɛnʃəl]  (adj.)  潛在的 (n.) 潛力
He is one of our potential customers. Make sure that you have a nice chat with them.
他是我們潛在的客戶之一，你可以好好地去跟他聊個天。

I am pretty sure that he has a potential to achieve what he wants.
我認為他有潛力可以達成他的夢想。

3 . least  最少 

least  [list]  (n.)  最少 
at least 至少
You have to be at least a hundred and ten centimeters to be on this roller coaster ride.
你搭雲霄飛車至少要110公分。

list  [lɪst]  (n.)  表、名冊 
Taylor Swift
Look what you make me do
I’ve got a list of names and yours is in red-underlined.
我有一份黑名冊，而你在我的黑名冊裡面被醒目的紅筆圈起來。

4 . risk  風險 

risk  [rɪsk]  (n.)  風險 
take a risk/ take the risk(特定的)冒險
If you want to buy a breakfast that you like, you are taking the risk of getting late at work.
如果上班的途中要買自己喜歡吃的早餐的話，就要冒上班可能會遲到的風險。

risky  [ˋrɪskɪ]  (adj.)  危險的 
It’s quite risky to drive in the dark without headlights.
如果你在黑暗中開車沒有開頭燈，是一件非常危險的事情。

The point for today is not to leave your recordings below, but to tell your class, friends or everyone around you that shopping actually reduces the risk of death but make sure that it says that you don’t necessarily have to buy anything, so don’t buy anything just because of today’s pronunciation challenge and Sam will challenge you guys tomorrow, bye!
今天的重點不是將你的錄音上傳到VT來，而是告訴你的班上同學、朋友或是你周遭的人：購物事實上會減少死亡的風險，但是請確保一點：你不需要非得買任何東西才能達到效果，所以千萬不要買任何東西，因為今天的口說挑戰告訴我們只需要花點時間出外走走就能達到效果了。Sam明天將會在口說挑戰與大家相見，BYE!