Homemade udon noodles are so much better than pre-made noodles, and the ingredients are actually very, very simple.
自家製的烏龍麵比現成的烏龍麵好很多喔！而且材料也非常簡單！
........................

1. _
  * homemade  [ˋhomˋmed]  (adj.)  自製的
    - Nothing beats my mom homemade cookies.
      + 沒有什麼能比我媽媽的自製餅乾更好。
    - These brownies are homemade.
      + 這些布朗尼是自製的。
  * handmade  [ˋhænd͵med]  (adj.)  手工的
    - This leather wallet is handmade.
      + 這款皮革錢包採用手工製作。

2. _
  * pre-made  (adj.)  預先做的
    - This grocery store sells some pre-made salads and sandwiches.
      + 這家雜貨店出售一些預製的沙拉和三明治。
  * packaged  [ˋpækɪdʒd]  (adj.)  包裝的
    - I try to eat fresh food rather than packaged food.
      + 我嘗試吃新鮮食物而不是包裝食物。

3. _
  * udon  (n.)  烏龍麵
    - I love the seafood udon from the Japanese place.
      + 我喜歡日本料理的海鮮烏冬面。
  * ramen  (n.)  拉麵
    - When I visit Japan, I always eat a lot of ramen.
      + 當我訪問日本時，我總是吃很多拉麵。
  * tempura  [ˋtɛmpʊrə]  (n.)  天婦羅
    - tempura (fry)
    - At Japan restaurant, I order tempura shrimp.
      + 在日本餐廳，我點了天婦羅蝦。

4. _
  * ingredient  [ɪnˋgridɪənt]  (n.)  原料
    - Shortbread cookies only have three ingredients sugar, butter, and flour.
      + Shortbread cookies只有糖，黃油和麵粉三種成分。
  * recipe  [ˋrɛsəpɪ]  (n.)  食譜
    - I found the recipe for chicken soup online.
      + 我在網上找到了雞湯的配方。