In other words, over-achievers are trying to solve a range of psychological problems through material or worldly means.

也就是說，過度成功者正在嘗試經由各種苦難去解決一連串心理層面的難關。


1. -
    * in other words  (phr.)  換句話說、也就是說
        - She is the best teacher. In other words, she is better than any other teacher in the school.
            + 她是最好的老師，換句話說，她比學校其他任何老師都好。
    * that is to say  (phr.)  就是、確切地說
        - You have to finish your homework in the three days. That is to say, you need to hand in the homework on Monday.
            + 你必須在三天內完成作業，也就是說你需要在周一交作業。

2. -
    * psychological  [͵saɪkəˋlɑdʒɪk!]  (adj.)  心理的、精神的
        - Nowadays, more and more people suffer from psychological problems.
            + 如今，越來越多的人患有心理問題。
    * physical  [ˋfɪzɪk!]  (adj.)  身體的、物理的、激烈的
        - physical education (PE)
        - I don't really enjoy physical activity.
            + 我並不喜歡運動。
        - This basketball game is starting to get a little too physical.
            + 這場籃球比賽開始變得非常激烈。

3. -
    * material  [məˋtɪrɪəl]  (adj.)  物質的、有形的、重大的
        - He is not interested in material wealth.
            + 他對物質財富不感興趣。
        - materialistic 拜金的
        - That witness is material to this case.
            + 那個目擊者對這個案子很重要。
    * spiritual  [ˋspɪrɪtʃʊəl]  (adj.)  心靈的
        - In the relationship, this spiritual connection matters to me the most.
            + 在談戀愛時，心靈的交流是最重要的

4. -
    * means  [minz]  (n.)  方法、財產
        - We need to find out other means of transportation.
            + 我們需要找出其他交通工具。
        - She is living beyond her means.
            + 她的生活支出超出了她的收入。
            + live beyond one's means 入不敷出
    * by all means  (phr.)  當然可以
        - Can I borrow your pen?
            + 我可以借你的鋼筆嗎？
        - By all means.
            + 當然可以