Unsurprisingly, capsule hotels are separated by gender, with this hotel keeping men and women on separated floors. The only space shared by everyone is the communal area.

一點也不意外的是，膠囊旅館的房間是男女分開的。我住的這家旅館，男女分在不同樓層。只有公共區域是共用的。

1. _
 * unsurprisingly [ʌnsəˋpraɪzɪŋlɪ] (adv.) 不足為奇地
 - The breakfast provided by the hotel is unsurprisingly plain.
 + 飯店提供的早餐很普通
 + plain => 很普通, 比起common, 有貶意
 * unsuspected [ʌnsəˋspɛktɪd] (adj.) 未知的
 - It was the unsuspected difficulties that hindered our investigation.
 + 這是一個意想不到的困難阻礙了我們的調查。
 + hinder => 阻礙

2. _
 * capsule [ˋkæps! ] (n.) 小容器；(藥) 膠囊
 - Capsule hotels are very popular in Tokyo because the accommodation fee there is really expensive.
 + 膠囊旅館在東京非常受歡迎，因為那裡的住宿費非常昂貴。
 + capsule hotels => 膠囊旅館
 + accommodation fee
 * captain [ˋkæptɪn] (v.) 擔任統帥、指揮
 - He captained the baseball team for two years when he was in college.
 + 他在大學期間擔任棒球隊隊長兩年。

3. _
 * separate [ˋsɛpə͵ret] (v.) 分離
 - My parents separated when I was five and they never got back together.
 + 我的父母分開時我五歲，他們之後沒有復合過。
 * desperate [ˋdɛspərɪt] (adj.) 絕望的
 - A desperate man can do anything, you can't even imagine.
 + 一個絕望的人可以做任何事情，你甚至無法想像。

4. _
 * share [ʃɛr] (v.) 分享、分擔
 - I share a room with my brother, but he is really the worst roommate in the world.
 + 我與我的兄弟分享房間，但他真的是世界上最差的室友。
 * sharpen [ˋʃɑrpn] (v.) 削尖；磨練
 - I need to sharpen my writing skills or I'll never pass the exam.
 + 我需要提高自己的寫作技巧，否則我將永遠不會通過考試。
 - sharpen the pecil.

5. _
 * communal [ˋkɑmjʊn] (adj.) 公共的、共同的
 - Please don't make loud noises in the communal area. It annoys people.
 + 請不要在公共區域發出大聲吵鬧的聲音。
 + make loud noise
 + communal area
 * commonwealth [ˋkɑmən͵wɛlθ] (n.) 共和國、公益
 - Canada is a commonwealth country.
 + 加拿大是一個共和國。