Rather than digging in the ground for the elements needed for new handsets, it makes sense to extract them from old phones. But only about 10% of handsets are recycled now. So recycle your phone if you get a new one this year. Why? It is, you might say, elementary.

比起挖掘土讓中所需的元素來製作新的手機，從舊的手機中提取它們更合理，但現在僅有大約 10% 的手機被回收。所以，如果你今年買了一隻新的，把你的手機拿去回收吧！為什麼？可以這麼說，這是非常基本的一件事 (諧音: 元素)

1. _
 * dig [dɪg] (v.) 挖掘
 - My dog dug a hole to bury the toys, but in the end, he forgot where the hole was.
 + 我的狗挖了一個洞來埋葬玩具，但最後，他忘記了洞的位置。
 * dip [dɪp] (v.) 浸、蘸
 - It tastes so much better if you dip it in the sauce.
 + 如果你把它浸在醬汁中，它的味道會好很多。

2. _
 * element [ˋɛləmənt] (n.) 【化】元素；要素
 - The key elements for a successful essay will be taught in class today.
 + 今天將在課堂上講授成功論文的關鍵要素。
 - key elements 關鍵要素
 * elementary [ɛləˋmɛntərɪ] (adj.) 基本的、基礎的
 - elementary school. 小學
 - This question is rather elementary for college students.
 + 對於大學生來說，這個問題相當簡單。

3. _
 * handset [ˋhænd͵sɛt] (n.) 手機；電話聽筒
 - This case can protect the screen of your handsets from getting scratched or broken.
 + 這種外殼可以保護您的手機屏幕免受劃傷或損壞。
 * headphones [ˋhɛd͵fonz] (n.) 頭戴式耳機
 - Don't wear your headphones for too long because it might deteriorate your hearing.
 + 請勿長時間佩戴耳機，因為這可能會使聽力受損。
 + deteriorate => 退化

4. _
 * extract [ɪkˋstrækt] (v.) 提取、提煉
 - His job is to extract oil from this site.
 + 他的工作是從這個地方提取石油。
 * abstract [ˋæbstrækt] (adj.) 抽象的；難懂的
 - The professor spent a lot of time elaborating on the abstract concept, yet students still didn't get it.
 + 教授花了很多時間詳細闡述抽象概念，但學生仍然沒有得到它。

5. _
 * recycle [ riˋsaɪk!] (v.) 回收
 - Japan has a complete recycling system. They recycle almost everything.
 + 日本有完整的回收系統，幾乎可以回收所有東西。
 * reuse [riˋjuz] (v.) 重複利用
 - You can protect your environment by following the three Rs, which stands for reuse, reduce and recycle.
 + 您可以通過遵循三個R來保護您的環境，這三個R代表重複使用，減少和再循環。