There is a big difference between your state of mind before you start working and your state of mind once you're in the flow state, once you're immersed in your project. The trick is just getting yourself there.

開始工作之前的心理狀態，以及全心投入的心理狀態之間有顯著的差異，一旦你全心埋首於你的專案。訣竅就只是讓自己達到那個目標。


1. _
 * difference [ˋdɪfərəns] (n.) 差別，差異
 - When you're in an exotic country, embracing the cultural differences can help you fit into the society a lot better.
 + cultural differences => 文化差異
 + fit into the society => 融入社會
 * differ [ˋdɪfɚ] (v.) 不同，相異
 - Though they are brothers, their appearances differ considerably from each other.
 + 雖然他們是兄弟，但他們的外表相差很大。

2. _
 * state of mind [] (ph.) 心情；心理狀態
 - Keeping yourself in a positive state of mind before the exam is very important.
 + 考試前保持積極的心態是非常重要的。
 * mindset [ˋmaɪnd͵sɛt] (n.) 思想傾向；思維方式
 - It's difficult to understand people because everyone has a different mindset.
 + 很難理解人，因為每個人都有不同的心態。

3. _
 * flow [flo] (n.) 流；流動
 - I want to feel the flow of blood and the blowing wind. It's how I know I'm alive.
 + 我想要感受血液的流動和吹風是我知道我活著的方式。 => 是還蠻浪漫的~
 * flourish [ˋflɝɪʃ] (v.) (植物等) 茂盛，繁茂
 - His company flourished over the past few years.
 + 他的公司在過去幾年裡蓬勃發展。
 + grow, prosper => 形容公司蓬勃發展

4. _
 * immerse [ɪˋmɝs] (v.) 使浸沒
 - When I was a kid, I immersed myself in the fantasy of Harry Potter's World.
 + 當我還是個孩子的時候，我沉浸在哈利波特世界的幻想中。
 * immense [ɪˋmɛns] (adj.) 巨大的；廣大的
 - I spent an immense amount of time on perfecting my project. Hopefully, my professor will like it.
 + 我花了很多時間來完善我的項目，希望我的教授會喜歡它。
 + immense amount of time => a lot of time

5. _
 * trick [trɪk] (n.) 詭計；騙局
 - Don't play any nasty tricks on me, or I will make you regret it.
 + 不要對我玩任何討厭的伎倆，否則我會讓你後悔。
 + play any nasty tricks on me => play trick on someone(固定用法)
 + I will make you regret it. => 強烈的語氣
 + You will regret it.
 * treat [trit] (n.) 請客
 - Don't worry about the money. It's my treat.
 + 不要擔心錢。 我請客。
 + trick or treat?