Thanks, Priscilla.
I think, I am not. I usually arrive on time unless I get lost.
.......................................................

1-1. underestimate [ˋʌndɚˋɛstə͵met] (v.)低估
→ Don't underestimate yourself by comparing yourself with successful people.
1-2. look down on (ph.)看不起；蔑視
→ They look down on her because she is poor and uneducated.
----------

2-1. show up (ph.)(尤指遲些時候或出其不意地) 到達、露面
→ Not many people showed up to the meeting this morning.
2-2. show off (ph.)炫耀；誇耀
→ She likes to wear really tight clothes to show off her nice body.
* show sth. off, show off sth.
----------

3-1. disrespect [dɪsrɪˋspɛkt] (n.)不敬；無禮
→ Going overtime when giving a speech is a sign of little preparation and disrespect for the audience.
* little preparation 幾乎沒有、否定
3-2. contempt [kənˋtɛmpt] (n.)輕視、蔑視
* 比disrespect再強烈、負面一些
→ She has nothing but contempt for those bullies. 
* bully (n.) 霸凌者
* bullied (adj.) 被霸凌的
----------

4-1. value [ˋvælju] (v.)尊重；重視
→ I value my parents' advice a lot and I definitely don't want to disappoint them.
* value sth. a lot 非常重視某個東西
* disappoint sb. 讓某人失望
* make sb. disappoint(X)不會這樣使用
4-2. esteem [ɪsˋtim] (v.)尊重；珍重
→ Everyone esteems his opinion more than all the other colleagues because he is the most trustworthy person in the office.
* trustworthy (adj.) 值得信賴的
----------

5-1. tremendously [trɪˋmɛndəslɪ] (adv.)極大地；極端地
→ He always failed these exams at school, but then, he became tremendously successful ten years later.
5-2. tremble [ˋtrɛmb!] (v.)發抖；震顫
→ He started to tremble uncontrollably when his abusive father walked in.
* abusive (adj.)虐待的
* uncontrollably (adv.) 無法控制地
.......................................................

And I always underestimate how long something is going to take. I don't like this about myself. I understand that me showing up late is seen as a sign of disrespect by people and it is! It is disrespectful. I feel terrible about that because I really respect the people I work with and I value them tremendously.

我總是低估某件事情需要花費的時間，也對這樣的自己感到不滿意。我知道遲到是對他人不尊重的表現，而且確實是這樣！這是不得體的。我感到很糟糕，因為我真的很尊敬跟我共事的人，也非常重視他們。