You may have heard that astronomers don't consider Pluto or its brethren to be planets. However, most planetary scientists still do, which is why we're using that terminology here.

你可能聽過有些天文學家不認為冥王星或它的兄弟不算行星。然而，大部分行星科學家還是把它算在內，這就是為什麼我們在這部影片中還是使用行星這個詞。

今日發音重點整理：
注意句子的重音，重音通常落在:
1.	實詞(content words) : 名詞、動詞、形容詞、副詞等等
2.	實詞中尤其想強調的字，在今天例句裡是may
註：與實詞對比的就是虛詞(function words): 像是介系詞(of, in, on)，連接詞(and, but)等等，通常不會放在重音。

☯心法：實字強高慢，虛字弱平快。
＃基本原則，動名形副疑問詞，音量強、語調高、速度慢，其餘弱平快。

1. _
 * astronomers [əˋstrɑnəmɚ] (n.) 天文學家
 - astronomer is someone who studies astronomy, not astrology but astronomy and astronomy is the study of space and the universe.
 - NASA employees a lot of astronomers.
 * astronomy [əsˋtrɑnəmɪ] (n.) 天文學
2. _
 * brethren [ˋbrɛðrən] (n.) 兄弟們
 - Brethren is actually not a word that is used often a brother in is kind of like a Brotherhood but in this case, it simply means its own kind or things that are similar to it.
 - I want to buy an expensive phone so you can say I want to buy an iPhone 10 or its brethren.
3. _
 * planetary [ˋplænə͵tɛrɪ] (adj.) 行星的
 - planetary means something to do with planets.
 - A system of the planets that we have would be called a planetary system.
4. _
 * terminology [͵tɝməˋnɑlədʒɪ] (n.) 術語；術語學
 - terminology are words that are used in a special area of knowledge like technical words. For example, words like verbs and adjectives are terminology that you would need to know if you want to study English grammar.
 * term [tɝm] (n.) 術語
 * jargon [ˋdʒɑrgən] (n.) 行話；黑話