But climate change is our new reality. And if we don’t take steps to mitigate it, we will continue to see powerful, severe hurricanes.
即使歷時不長，氣候變遷已是事實。倘若我們未採取措施，想辦法減輕其危害，我們就會持續碰上強大、劇烈的颶風。

1. _
 * climate change [] (phr.) 氣候變化
 - Climate refers to the general weather conditions of a certain's area.
 * global warming [] (phr.) 全球暖化
 - For example, Taiwan is quite hot and wet weather for most of the year, so you can say that Taipei has a hot and wet climate. The more scientific term for this is a subtropical climate. The climate change is also often called global warming because the general trend of the climate is getting warmer.

2. _
 * mitigate [ˋmɪtə͵get] (v.) 使緩和；減輕
 - it means to lessen the impact of in other words it is to make something less serious or less painful.
 - We pair this word with a problem, so we can say to mitigate a problem which means to make a problem better.
 + mitigate a problem => 更好的解決問題
 * reduce [rɪˋdjus] (v.) 減少
 * alleviate [əˋlivɪ͵et] (v.) 使緩和；減輕
 - Other words for mitigate include reduce, alleviate or lessen.
3. _
 * severe [səˋvɪr] (n.) 嚴重的
 * severity [səˋvɛrətɪ] (n.) 嚴格；嚴重
 - It means strong but in a more serious or negative way. For example, you can call a strong storm a severe storm or you can call a strong hurricane of a severe hurricane.
 - If your eye hurts a lot, you can say that I have a severe pain in my eye and I need to go to the hospital.

hurricane, typhoon, cyclone