If you see an asterisk on the price tag, that's your cue to stock up! According to Consumerist, an asterisk means that the item has hit its lowest price and won't be getting restocked.

如果你在標價上看到一個「星號」，那就是在提醒你一定要買。根據 Consumerist ，「星號」表示那樣商品正在最低價的特價中，而且不會再進貨了。


1. _
 * asterisk [ˋæstə͵rɪsk] (n.) (表示下有注釋或單詞中字母的缺失的) 星號 (*)
 - Where is the asterisk on this keyboard?
 + 鍵盤上的星號在哪裡？
 - hashtag # => octothorpe, 井字號

2. _
 * price tag [] (n.) (掛在商品上的) 價格標籤
 - name tag => 名牌
 - dog tag => 身分標籤
 - Sarah couldn't find the price tag for this dress.
 + Sarah找不到這件衣服的價格標籤。

3. _
 * cue [kju] (n.) 暗示；信號
 - When you hear a beep that is your cue to get him the mic.
 + 當你聽到一聲嗶嗶聲，這是讓他獲得麥克風的提示。
 - Cue to cue => 從一個cue到下一個cue

4. _
 * stock up [] (phr.) 大量購買；囤積
 - People started to stock up loads and loads of toilet paper after they heard the rumor about the increase of the price.
 + 在聽到有關價格上漲的傳聞後，人們開始儲存大量的衛生紙。
 * restock [riˋstɑk] (v.) 進貨；補貨
 - The store isn't planning on restocking the product as the sales weren't very good.
 + 由於銷售不是很好，商店不計劃補貨。

5. _
 * according to [] (phr.) 根據；按照；取決於
 - According to this research, more than thirty percent of Americans aren't brushing their teeth enough.
 + 根據這項研究，超過30％的美國人沒有足夠的刷牙。