Hi, guys. You're listening to today's pronunciation challenge, and my name is Kristi, and Today's video is called "Why nice people are scary," and I don't know if you have this sort of experience or not, but sometimes when you meet (umm) perhaps (ugh) you see someone new and you think they're extremely nice, and you suddenly you have this doubt for yourself.


1-1 totally (adv.) 完全地
ex1: "Aren't you in love with Taylor Swift?" "Totally!!!"
ex2: A lot of people are totally obsessed with the new app Pokemon Go.

1-2 total (adj.) 總計的
ex: That will be £62 in total.

2-1 affection (n.) 愛慕

2-2 affect (v.) 影響
ex: His mood was completely affected by the fight with his girlfriend the night before and therefore he lost the competition.

2-3 effect (n.) 結果；效益
* Butterfly Effect 蝴蝶效應
* Ripple Effect 漣漪效應- = chain reaction連鎖效應

3-1 unnerving (a.) 令人緊張不安的

3-2 nerve racking (a.) 令人不安的
ex: Stop fiddling(微不足道的) with that pen! It's very nerve racking.

3-3 nervous (adj.) 緊張的

4-1 unsettling (adj.) 使人不安的

4-2 settle (v.) 安排
ex1: Once you settle down in L.A., give me a phone call.
ex2: I think it's finally time to settle down.

4-3 Seattle (n.) 西雅圖
* Chicago (n.) 芝加哥

5-1 trick (n.) 詭計
ex: Street performers in London or Paris often trick you into taking a photo with them and asking you for money.

5-2 treat (v.) 對待；請客
* trick or treat 不給糖就搗蛋
ex1: You should treat others the way you wish to be treated.
ex2: It's my treat. 


Alright so that's pretty much for today's pronunciation challenge, but this video is basically telling us that, you know, it's okay when you're loved or when a person who's all nice, who's incredibly nice, loves you back as well because (I just) it happens sometimes and you don't have to doubt their love or anything behind. Okay, so hope you guys enjoy today's video, and I will challenge you guys tomorrow, bye.
