Next, frequent repetitions with allotted breaks are common practice habits of elite performers. Studies have shown that many top athletes, musicians, and dancers spend 50-60 hours per week on activities related to their craft. 
Many divide their time used for effective practice into multiple daily practice sessions of limited duration.

接著，頻繁的反覆練習和分配休息時間，是頂尖表演者常見的訓練習慣。研究指出，許多頂尖的運動員、音樂家與舞者，每週花五十到六十小時在磨練領域相關的技藝。許多人將有效運用的時間分成每日多個限時練習時段。


1. _
 * allot [ə'lɑt] (v.) （尤指將現有的東西）分配；分派
 - it means to assign or distribute a portion of something to someone.
 - You should allot roughly sixty thousand dollars a year for insurance, taxes and any association fees.
 + 你應該每年分配大約六萬美元的保險稅和任何協會費用。
 * allotment [ə'lɑtmənt] (n.) 分配，份額
 - I'm about to use up this year's allotment of vacation days.
 + 我準備用掉今年的假期日。

2. _
 * elite [ɪ'lit] (n.) 精英；掌權人
 - The word has two meanings. One is referring to a group of people who are often to be the best educated, the best-trained and which makes them somehow superior than others.
 - The winners of the science contest represent the elite of our country.
 + 科學競賽的獲勝者代表了我們國家的精英。
 - the other meaning is referring to the riches, the most powerful group of people in a society.
 - The elites at the top of the pyramid are formed by the banking families.
 + 金字塔頂端的精英由銀行家庭組成。
 * elitist [i'litɪst] (adj.) 精英統治的；精英主義的
 - I don't know since when this word started to become a pejorative term. It's basically describing a small group of people who have a lot of advantages of power and money.
 - I don't want to sound like an elitist snob, but that's not exactly a ton of money.
 + 我不想听起來像精英勢利小人，但這不是一大筆錢。

3. _
 * duration [djʊ'reʃən] (n.) 持續時間
 - the ability to last for a length of time.
 - Walking breaks allow you to increase the duration of your workout.
 + 步行休息可以增加鍛煉的持續時間。
 * durable ['djʊrəb!] (adj.) 耐久的
 - It's strong enough to last for a long time without breaking
 - It is made of durable material.
 + 它由耐用的材料製成