I want to apologize to to Ms Amundson, my ESL teacher. She used to send me to go get cigarettes from the liquor store, and I would steal two or three cigarettes, you know. And that’s the way I learned how to smoke, you know.

我想跟我的英文第二外語課程老師， Amundson 小姐說對不起。她之前都會請我幫她去商店買菸，然後我會偷個兩三根，我就是這樣學會抽煙的。



1. _
 * ESL [] (n.) 專給母語非英語的人的英語課程
 - ESL is usually used as an adjective so I am an ESL teacher and I'm teaching ESL students. Actually, I had a lot of experience with this word ESL and that was because I lived in a kind of like an Asian immigrant Community when I was in Canada.
2. _
 * cigarrete [͵sɪgəˋrɛt] (n.) 香菸
 - People consume when they have a smoke now.
 - If you look at this word actually it's quite interesting because there is a suffix on it. Which is the 'e-t-t-e' at the end of the word. It's the 'e-t-t-e' at the end of the word and the purpose of this suffix is to denote like a smaller version of a bigger thing. For example, let me give you another word with the ending like kitchenette. That is a small kitchen so it's like a smaller version of a regular sized the kitchen. And in this word cigarette, it's like a cigar but it's a smaller version of a cigar so that's quite interesting.
 * cigar [sɪˋgɑr] (n.) 雪茄
 * nicotine [ˋnɪkə͵tin] (n.) 尼古丁
 * tobacco [təˋbæko] (n.) 菸草
3. _
 * liquor [ˋlɪkɚ] (n.) 酒；烈酒
 - Be careful here with the pronunciation its q-u- o-r but it's actually just liquor right. Liquor means alcohol but you know it's actually usually used to denote hard liquor. Hard liquor meaning like a very strong alcoholic drink something like vodka or whiskey can be called liquor. In a place that sells liquor is called a liquor store but I think that's all.
 * alcohol [ˋælkə͵hɔl] (n.) 酒精；酒
 * vodka [ˋvɑdkə] (n.) 伏特加酒
 * whisky [ˋhwɪskɪ] (n.) 威士忌酒