Along with barbed wire fences, the Germans had sunk microphones nine feet deep into the soil all along the perimeter in order to detect the sound of digging.

除了鐵絲網護欄下方之外，德軍沿著護欄周邊將麥克風埋到九尺深的地底，以便偵測挖掘的聲音。


1. _
 * barbed wire fence [] (n.) 有刺鐵絲網
 - The prison is surrounded by barbed wire fences, so no one can get in or get out without permission.
 + 監獄被鐵絲網圍住，因此沒有人可以在未經允許的情況下進入或離開。
2. _
 * sink [sɪŋk] (v.) (使) 沈沒；(使) 陷入
 - sink, sank, sunk
 - The ship sank into the bottom of the ocean and was never seen again.
 + 船沉入海底，再也沒見過。
3. _
 * foot [fʊt] (n.) 呎；英尺
 - six-foot pole. => 複合形容詞
 - The length of the tunnel lasts about 20 feet.
 + 隧道長度約為20英尺。
4. _
 * soil [sɔɪl] (n.) 泥土；土壤
 - The material on the surface of the ground.
 - soil, earth, dirt
 - The farmer loosened the soil so that the crops can grow better.
 + 農民放鬆土壤，使作物生長得更好。
 + 農作物 => crops
 + farm produce
5. _
 * in order to [] (phr.) 為了；以便
 - Sammy kept the windows shut in order to keep flies out of the house.
 + Sammy閉緊了窗戶，以便將蒼蠅趕出家門。
 + shut => 緊閉，較為強烈的語氣
 - close
 - shut down => 關機
6. _
 * detect [dɪˋtɛkt] (v.) (尤指用特殊方法) 發現；察覺；看出
 - According to scientific research, some sounds cannot be detected by the human ear.
 + 根據科學研究，人耳無法檢測到一些聲音。