A dream is a succession of images, ideas, emotions, and sensations that occur in the mind during certain stages of sleep. Why we dream is not fully understood, though dreams have been a topic of scientific, philosophical and religious interest throughout history.

在特定的睡眠階段，我們會做夢。夢是由一連串的意象、靈感、情緒、情感所組成。為何我們會做夢還沒有完全找到原因，即使這些夢涵蓋各種主題，包含科學、哲學和歷史上的宗教趣事。

1. _
 * succession [səkˋsɛʃən] (n.) 連續
 - A succession of bad news strikes and overwhelms her.
 + 一連串的壞消息襲來並壓倒了她。
 * successive [səkˋsɛsɪv] (adj.) 連續的、相繼的
 - The football team won championship for the fourth successive year.
 + 足球隊連續四年奪得冠軍。
 + ...successive year. => 連續幾年

2. _
 * sensation [sɛnˋseʃən] (n.) 感覺、知覺
 - I have no sensation (no feeling) for those sad romantic movies. They just seem too phony (fake) to me.
 + 我對那些悲傷的浪漫電影沒有任何感覺（沒有感覺），對我來說只是虛假（假）。
 - no sensation = no feeling
 - phony = fake
 * sense [sɛns] (n.) 感官；官能
 - She has a good sense of taste, so she aims to become a professional food critic.
 + 她有很好的品味，所以她的目標是成為一名專業的食品評論家。
 + sense of taste => 好的味覺, sense of ...
 + aims to become => 目標成為
 + food critic => 美食評論員

3. _
 * occur [əˋkɝ] (v.) 發生；出現
 - If something occurred to you during the experiment, you should tell me immediately.
 + 如果您在實驗期間發生了某些事情，您應該立即告訴我。
 * occupy [ˋɑkjə͵paɪ] (v.) 佔(時間、空間)
 - I'm occupied in work, so I can't attend the party tonight.
 + 我今晚忙於工作，所以我無法出席今晚的派對。
 + I'm occupied => I'm busy.

4. _
 * stage [stedʒ] (n.) 階段；時期
 - At this stage of life, people often feel confused and lack of confidence, but we should always remember that there are people who love us and care about us.
 + 在你生命的這個階段，人們常常感到困惑和缺乏自信，但我們應該永遠記住，有些人愛我們，關心我們。
 + At this stage of life => 在這生命階段
 + feel confused 感到困惑
 + lack of confidence 缺乏自信
 * stagnant [ˋstægnənt] (adj.) 不流動的，停滯的
 - I'm in the stagnant phase of improving my English for a long time.
 + 我很長一段時間處於提高英語水平的停滯階段。
 + stagnant phase => 停滯期
 - stagnant water

5. _
 * philosophical [fɪləˋsɑfɪ!] (adj.) 哲學的
 - This book inspired me a lot because the dialogues are very philosophical.
 + 這本書給了我很多啟發，因為對話是非常哲學的。
 + inspired me 啟發我