There are apparently over 80,000 Chinese characters, which can seem pretty intimidating – but guess what you only need to know 3,500 in Standard Chinese. This might still seem like a lot, but you can actually get by with only 1,000 of the most frequent characters.

中文字有超過八萬個，似乎很令人卻步，但是你只需要知道官話的 3500 字就好。好像還是很多，但其實掌握 1000 個最常用的字就沒問題。


1. _
 * apparently [əˋpærəntlɪ] (adv.) 顯然地；似乎、表面上
 - As far as I know. So it's not exactly scientific. I don't know for certain but it's true. As far as I know or according to what I can see. So I can say apparently it's gonna rain later. Do I know a hundred percent that it's gonna rain. I don't. But apparently it's going to. Maybe I heard it somewhere or maybe I saw it on the weather report.
 * evidently [ˋɛvədəntlɪ] (adv.) 明顯地

2. _
 * intimidating [ɪnˋtɪmə͵detɪŋ] (adj.) 令人生畏的
 - Something is intimidating it's kind of scary. And it's scary to the point where it begins to have power over you. For example, if I feel like a police officer is intimidating. That means I feel like the police officer is kind of scary or can maybe hurt me if he wanted to.
 * scary [ˋskɛrɪ] (adj.) 引起驚慌的
 * frightening [ˈfraɪtnɪŋ ] (adj.) 使人驚嚇的

3. _
 * get by [] (v.) (勉強) 對付過去；(勉強) 過活
 - Get by means to accomplish something but with a little bit of difficulty. So if I say that I have just enough money to get by. It means that I'm struggling a little bit to live with the money that I have. I can still do it but it's kind of a struggle. And in the passage, it says that she can get by knowing about a thousand Chinese characters which means that with those 1000 Chinese characters you can kind of read and write Chinese and communicate effectively but it would still be difficult at times.
 * cope [kop] (v.) 對付；應付
 * scrape by [] (v.) 勉強維持；勉強度日；勉強通過

4. _
 * frequently [ˋfrikwəntlɪ] (adv.) 頻繁地
 - Means often and regularly. So if I say that I practice piano frequently it means that maybe I practice piano every day or maybe every other day.
 * regularly [ˋrɛgjəlɚlɪ] (adv.) 有規律地；定期地