We read fiction for many reasons. To be entertained, to find out who done it, to travel to strange, new planets, to be scared, to laugh, to cry, to think, to feel, to be so absorbed that for a while we forget where we are.

我們為了種種的理由而看小說。為了娛樂自己，為了找出嫌疑犯，為了旅行到一個陌生的新星球，為了被嚇，為了開懷大笑，為了放聲大哭，為了思考，為了感受，為了沉浸其中而暫時忘記身在何處。

1. _
 * fiction ['fɪkʃən] (n.) 小說：虛構的事
 - Science Fiction and fantasy are the most popular genres in fiction.
 + 科幻小說和幻想是小說中最受歡迎的類型。
 *science fiction ['saɪəns 'fɪkʃən] (n.) 科幻小說
 *fantasy ['fæntəsi] (n.) 奇幻小說
 *genre ['ʒɑnrə] (n.) 文類；體裁

2. _
 * entertain [ɛntɚ'ten] (v.) 使有興趣；使快樂：款待
 - To keep people enjoying themselves.
 * entertaining [,ɛntɚ'tenɪŋ] (adj.) 有趣的
 - The book or the film is very entertaining.
 - Are there any entertaining things to do for this weekend?
 + 這個週末有什麼有趣的事情要做嗎？


3. _
 * absorb [əb'zɔrb] (v.) 吸收；理解；使全神貫注
 - You can say human brain absorbs things. Just like kids can absorb whatever they hear quickly. They still got the languages like sponges. They absorb new information like sponges.
 * be absorbed in [bi əb'zɔrb ɪn] (.) 被…吸引住；全神貫注於
 - I was so absorbed in my work that I lost track of time.
 + 我非常專注於工作，以至於忘記了時間。
 * absorbing [əb'zɔrbɪŋ] (adj.) 引人入勝的
 - It means something that is so interesting that is fully taking someone's attention.
 - This book is very absorbing. It has absorbing plots.
 + 這本書非常吸引人，它有吸引人的情節。