More than a million Venezuelans have moved to Colombia in recent years. And in an era of record setting migration, when borders seem to be getting thicker, harder to cross, Colombia is doing something that you don't see very often. It's opening its doors and it's letting people in.

近幾年，超過百萬名委內瑞拉人已經搬離至哥倫比亞，在這個移民潮創紀錄的時期，當邊境人潮越來越多，越難跨越時，哥倫比亞卻在做反常的舉動，它在打開國門，讓人們進來。


1. _
 * era ['ɪrə] (n.) 時代；年代
 - era is referring to a period of time in the history that has a distinct quality or feature.
 - It's the end of an era.
 + 一個時代的結束。
 - When my favorite TV series, "Friends" finished filming, it's like the end of an era to me.
 + 當我最喜歡的電視連續劇"六人行"完結時，對我來說就像是一個時代的結束。

2. _
 * set a record [sɛt ə 'rɛkɚd] (phr.) 創紀錄
 - If you can achieve something no one has ever achieved, you set the record.
 - Our lovely Winnie sets the record for the most viewed videos on Voicetube.
 + 我們可愛的Winnie創下了在Voicetube上觀看次數最多的視頻紀錄。

3. _
 * migration [maɪ'greʃən] (n.) 遷移
 - The mean is movement from one place to another.
 - Animal migration.
 - Human migration that is a movement of a group of people to a new place or country in order to find better living conditions like what Venezuelans are going through right now.
 * refugee [,rɛfjʊ'dʒi] (n.) 難民；避難者；逃亡者
 - Refugees are people who are forced to flee to a foreign country to escape from threatening situations in their homeland.
 - Do you know how many refugees there are in the world right now?
 - There are 68.5 million people around the world who have been forced to flee from their home due to violent conflicts 68.5 million.
 - => morale lifting.

4. _
 * border ['bɔrdɚ] (n.) 邊界；國界
 - border means the line that divides two countries.
 - Many North Koreans who fled across the border spent years living underground in China.
 + 許多逃離邊境的朝鮮人在中國躲藏多年。
 + underground in China => 非正常入境，人口黑數
 + Defector => 叛逃者, 脫北者(North Korean Defector)
