Thank Daniel, this video is very useful.

A lot of people think if I success, I will be happier, but now this theory maybe is wrong. 
Some research find if you are happier or more positive, you will increase your success and the video 
provides us some tips to improve our positivity.
1. 3 gratitudes
2. journaling
3. exercise
4. meditation
5. random acts of kindness

If someone wants to see the full video, you can click this link.
https://goo.gl/Ig7aTL

之前不知道是不是有VT的人推薦過他的書"哈佛最受歡迎的快樂工作學"，有機會可以去看看
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
1-1. present (adj.)  [prez.ənt]現在，目前
I'm present, we are currently working on developing new product. 
1-2. present (n.)  禮物，贈品
Thank you for this present. I will treasure it forever.
1-3. presently (adv.)  現在，目前
Presently, we are recruiting for new employees. Please check out our website for more details.
1-4. preset (v.)  事先裝置，預先調整
The water should be heated quickly to a preset temperature. 
1-5. present [prɪˈzent] (v.) 呈現; 給
The winners were presented with medals.
+++

2-1. successfully (adv.)  順利地，成功地
We successfully went to the moon in 1969.
2-2. success (n.)  成功，成就
The party was a huge success. (This huge voice seems like to mimic Donald Trump)
+++

3-1. dopamine (n.)  多巴胺
Dopamine is an important chemical from in the brain.
+++

4-1. function (n.)  官能，功能，作用
The function of the hot is to pump blood through the body.
4-2. functional (adj.)  機能的
The building design is not only functional, but also beautiful.
+++

5-1. center (adj.)  中樞，核心
The staircase is in the center of the building.
5-2. center  (v.)  把。。。放在中部
Please can you center the picture on the wall?
5-3. centered (adj.)  有圓心的
This is a family center hotel, so you can't have a party here.
5-4. off-center (adj.)  偏離中央的
The mirror over the sink is a little bit off-center.
+++

6-1. system (n.)  身體，全身
The disease affected her entire system.
6-2. systematic (adj.)  有系統的，成體系的
We used a systematic approach to solve the problem.
6-3. systematically
We approached the problem systematically.