謝謝Kristi，不確定是不是改版的影響，之前沒注意，有些人錄音留言的英文句子過長，最後的單字會被截成2個單字

This video told us food wastage includes growing, processing... etc. If we can find the way to save this food, we can save the lots of evironmental cost, but now we need to reduce the food wastage by ourselves.

----------------------------------------
1-1. world [wɝld] (n.)  世界 
1-2. word [wɝd] (n.)  單字
+++++

2-1. produce [prəˋdjus]  (v.)  出產
This factory produces high quality food.
2-2. produce [ˋprɑdjus]  (n.)  農產品
This farm is known for their dairy produce.
2-3. product (n.)  產品
During evaluation, the quality of the product is often most important.
2-4. production (n.)  生產、製作
That actor broke his leg during production.
+++++

3-1. loss (n.)  喪失
I'm very sorry for your loss.
3-2. lost (adj.)  迷失的
I'm very a little bit lost about life recently.
3-3. lose (v.)  弄失
Never put your phone in the pocket when you're traveling in the Europe because you might lose your phone.
+++++

4-1. waste [west] (v.)  浪費
a. All his effort was wasted.
1. wastage (n.) 浪費
4-2. west [wɛst] (n.)  西方
4-3. waist (n.)  腰部
+++++

5-1. economic (adj.)  經濟實惠的
People might thought that men are being romantic, but actually they are just economic.
5-2. economy (n.)  節約
economy class
+++++

6-1. transport (v.)  運送
6-2. transporation (n.)  輸送
mass transportation system 
6-3. transfer (v.)  搬、轉換
Would you like to transfer this file?
Would you like to transfer this Pokemon to the professor?
6-4. transact (v.)  交易
1. transaction (n.)  交易
