Can you solve "Einstein's riddle"?
Part of the trick is to use the process of elimination and lots of trial and error to hone in on the right pieces, and the more logic puzzles you solve, the better your intuition will be for when and where there's enough information to make your deductions.
常用的技巧就是排除法和多次嘗試去找到正確的方向，解開的謎題越多，你的直覺就會更加敏銳，你就知道如何使用已知信息推斷。

There's an elimination test.

"Once you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains, no matter how improbable, must be the truth." - Arthur Conan Doyle quotes

Trial and error.

Trial period試用期

The dog left a wet trail(痕跡) on the carpet.

A trail(小徑) in the woods.

Tuition fee.

When you deduct the cost from the gains, you'll get the profit.

Further deduction(進一步降價).