You can practice a skill, a routine and a lot of things. This can apply to learning languages or apply to learning how to play a certain kind of sport, jogging or anything like that.

They need to rehearse in order to prepare for the interview. 

You can rehearse your speech, rehearse your lines for a play or for a movie.

You really impress me today.

He is a very impressive individual.

Someone leaves an impression on you. That just means that they did something that was significant or different, something out of ordinary(usually good) to let you remember that person or whatever they did.

Can I ask you an question?

He seems like a nice person, but I question his honesty and sincerity.

He usually a very honest businessman, but his recent deals seem a little bit questionable.